<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
	<channel>
		<title>Radio.com Reverse Chron Feed</title>
		<description>Most recent content from Radio.com</description>
		<link>https://dev-clay.radio.com</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 17:39:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
		<copyright>2019</copyright>
		<generator>Feed delivered by Clay</generator>
		<category>Voodoo,Simpsons</category>
		<category>Voodoo,Star Wars</category>
		<category>Voodoo</category>
		<category>Voodoo,Rock</category>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[The Simpsons is Somehow Still on and Monika was here]]></title>
			<link>https://dev-clay.radio.com/cereal/lucky-charms/the-simpsons-is-somehow</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dev-clay.radio.com/cereal/lucky-charms/the-simpsons-is-somehow</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl>http://www.thesimpsons.com</syndicatedUrl>
			<description><![CDATA[The Simpsons is Somehow Still on The Air TADA]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p>Save me, Jeebus. Yes! I am a citizen! Now which way to the welfare office? I'm kidding, I'm kidding. I work, I work. Stan Lee never left. I'm afraid his mind is no longer in mint condition. Brace yourselves gentlemen. According to the gas chromatograph, the secret ingredient is… Love!? Who's been screwing with this thing?</p>
  <p>Well, he's kind of  had it in for me ever since I accidentally ran over his dog. Actually,  replace &quot;accidentally&quot; with &quot;repeatedly&quot; and replace &quot;dog&quot; with &quot;son.&quot;  That's why I love elementary school, Edna. The children believe anything  you tell them.</p>
  <p>Donuts. Is there anything they can't do?  Weaseling out of things is important to learn. It's what separates us  from the animals…except the weasel. Dear Mr. President, There are too  many states nowadays. Please, eliminate three. P.S. I am not a crackpot.</p>
  <p>A  lifetime of working with nuclear power has left me with a healthy green  glow…and left me as impotent as a Nevada boxing commissioner. A woman  is a lot like a refrigerator. Six feet tall, 300 pounds…it makes ice.</p>
  <p>Please  do not offer my god a peanut. Our differences are only skin deep, but  our sames go down to the bone. Your guilty consciences may make you vote  Democratic, but secretly you all yearn for a Republican president to  lower taxes, brutalize criminals, and rule you like a king!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl></stationUrl>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline>D&apos;oh!</subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[The Simpsons is Somehow]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://stg-images.radio.com/aiu-media/MV5BMTE2ZWU2N2UtZjMzMS00NWViLTgwZTQtYzQ2OTc1YzNjMzk5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzU1NzE3NTgV1CR045480270ALUX477CR00477268AL-68c3159b-ff0f-493e-b9f4-ce92f21fbae8.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>true</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject" data-editable="inlinestuff">
    <div class="image-wrapper">
        
          <img src="https://stg-images.radio.com/aiu-media/MV5BMTE2ZWU2N2UtZjMzMS00NWViLTgwZTQtYzQ2OTc1YzNjMzk5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzU1NzE3NTgV1CR045480270ALUX477CR00477268AL-79d186a0-17f2-4805-b004-83df900122e4.jpg?width=800" alt="The Simpsons">
        
    </div>
</div>]]></lead>
			<category>Voodoo</category>
			<category>Simpsons</category>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Watch: Teen gets into Swordfight with Ghost]]></title>
			<link>https://dev-clay.radio.com/news/mma-wwe/star-wars-kid</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 15:43:11 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dev-clay.radio.com/news/mma-wwe/star-wars-kid</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl/>
			<description><![CDATA[Star Ward Kid youtube video]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p>The plans you refer to will soon be back in our hands. Still, she's got a lot of spirit. I don't know, what do you think? I find your lack of faith disturbing. You mean it controls your actions? Dantooine. They're on Dantooine.</p>
  <p>In my experience, there is no such thing as luck.  You mean it controls your actions? The plans you refer to will soon be  back in our hands. No! Alderaan is peaceful. We have no weapons. You  can't possibly…</p>
  <p>Don't underestimate the Force. Ye-ha! I find your  lack of faith disturbing. Hey, Luke! May the Force be with you. No!  Alderaan is peaceful. We have no weapons. You can't possibly… Obi-Wan is  here. The Force is with him.</p>
  <p>I'm surprised you had the courage  to take the responsibility yourself. Escape is not his plan. I must face  him, alone. I find your lack of faith disturbing. Leave that to me.  Send a distress signal, and inform the Senate that all on board were  killed.</p>
  <p>Don't act so surprised, Your Highness. You weren't on any  mercy mission this time. Several transmissions were beamed to this ship  by Rebel spies. I want to know what happened to the plans they sent  you. Don't act so surprised, Your Highness. You weren't on any mercy  mission this time. Several transmissions were beamed to this ship by  Rebel spies. I want to know what happened to the plans they sent you.</p>
  <p>No!  Alderaan is peaceful. We have no weapons. You can't possibly… A tremor  in the Force. The last time I felt it was in the presence of my old  master. All right. Well, take care of yourself, Han. I guess that's what  you're best at, ain't it?</p>
  <p>Alderaan? I'm not going to Alderaan.  I've got to go home. It's late, I'm in for it as it is. He is here. I'm  trying not to, kid. Look, I ain't in this for your revolution, and I'm  not in it for you, Princess. I expect to be well paid. I'm in it for the  money.</p>
  <p>Leave that to me. Send a distress signal, and inform the  Senate that all on board were killed. I find your lack of faith  disturbing. I suggest you try it again, Luke. This time, let go your  conscious self and act on instinct.</p>
  <p>No! Alderaan is peaceful. We  have no weapons. You can't possibly… She must have hidden the plans in  the escape pod. Send a detachment down to retrieve them, and see to it  personally, Commander. There'll be no one to stop us this time!</p>
  <p>Dantooine.<br /> They're on Dantooine. Ye-ha! As you wish. Your eyes can deceive you.  Don't trust them. What good is a reward if you ain't around to use it?  Besides, attacking that battle station ain't my idea of courage. It's  more like…suicide.</p>
  <p>I have traced the Rebel spies to her. Now she  is my only link to finding their secret base. Dantooine. They're on  Dantooine. Look, I can take you as far as Anchorhead. You can get a  transport there to Mos Eisley or wherever you're going.</p>
  <p>Remember,  a Jedi can feel the Force flowing through him. I don't know what you're  talking about. I am a member of the Imperial Senate on a diplomatic  mission to Alderaan-- Obi-Wan is here. The Force is with him.</p>
<aside class="component--tweet">
  <blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Anakin made of pictures of sand <a href="https://t.co/uoOY9h9ljs">pic.twitter.com/uoOY9h9ljs</a></p>&mdash; Star Wars Memes (@jedimemes) <a href="https://twitter.com/jedimemes/status/969229020712742913?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 1, 2018</a></blockquote>

</aside>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl/>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline>No spirits were harmed</subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[Star Wars Kid]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://stg-images.radio.com/aiu-media/ghyslaintransNvBQzQNjv4BqAdw0VrjqLWSqJHfZ45Ae0ZZleb6bWx1d7hBxM3Lz0SM-3f39fe18-2e82-40fd-8e9c-97590f294ed8.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>true</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[
  <div class="component--youtube"
      data-element-id="youtube-player-4o9dEsS3"
      data-content-id="3GJOVPjhXMY"
      data-autoplay-next-video="true"
      data-autoplay-video="false"
      data-playlist=""
      data-track-video-type="Editorial"
      data-track-video-location="article"
      data-track-video-title="Star Wars kid Drunken Jedi"
      data-track-video-duration="35"
      data-track-channel-name="fantom81z28"
      data-editable="inline"
      data-origsrc="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3GJOVPjhXMY">

    <iframe id="youtube-player-4o9dEsS3" type="text/html" width="640" height="360"
      src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3GJOVPjhXMY?autoplay=0&origin=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3GJOVPjhXMY"
      frameborder="0"></iframe>
  </div>
]]></lead>
			<category>Voodoo</category>
			<category>Star Wars</category>
			<editorialFeeds>Throwbacks</editorialFeeds>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Image Cover Test Import]]></title>
			<link>https://dev-clay.radio.com/sports/seo2</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 16:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dev-clay.radio.com/sports/seo2</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl/>
			<description><![CDATA[Despacito]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="component--subheader">
    <h2 class="headline">Five hours? Aw, man! Couldn&#x27;t you just get me the death penalty?</h2>
</div>
  <p>I  barely knew Philip, but as a clergyman I have no problem telling his  most intimate friends all about him. Yes, I saw. You were doing well,  until everyone died. Alright, let's mafia things up a bit. Joey, burn  down the ship. Clamps, burn down the crew.</p>
  <p>Leela, Bender, we're going grave robbing. <strong> Also Zoidberg.</strong> <em> Shut up and take my money!</em>  But, like most politicians, he promised more than he could deliver.</p>
<div class="component--subheader">
    <h2 class="headline">Daylight and everything.</h2>
</div>
  <p>Nay,  I respect and admire Harold Zoid too much to beat him to death with his  own Oscar. We'll need to have a look inside you with this camera. Hey,  guess what you're accessories to. Well, thanks to the Internet, I'm now  bored with sex. Is there a place on the web that panders to my lust for  violence?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl></stationUrl>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline>Lets see it</subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[Cover image Test]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://radioimg.s3.amazonaws.com/winsam/styles/nts_image_cover_tall_775x425/s3/Madonna_5_3.jpg?yDm86AOLDahtpDAErRars2NK_0zGri_W&amp;itok=PcXkt1az</coverImage>
			<featured>false</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject" data-editable="inlinestuff">
    <div class="image-wrapper">
        
          <img src="https://stg-images.radio.com/aiu-media/McChickenSandwich-76fb0dee-e522-48e1-a29b-6a413f48931e.png?width=800" alt="Its a McChicken">
        
    </div>
</div>]]></lead>
			<category>Voodoo</category>
			<editorialFeeds>CHR / Top 40</editorialFeeds>
			<editorialFeeds>Hot AC / Top 40 / CHR</editorialFeeds>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Featured? Syndicated? This Article is BOTH!]]></title>
			<link>https://dev-clay.radio.com/news/entertainment-news/testingcanonandfeature</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 14:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dev-clay.radio.com/news/entertainment-news/testingcanonandfeature</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl>https://1010wins.radio.com/articles/michael-cohen-says-hell-fill-blanks-mueller-report-redactions-soon-i-will-tell-it-all</syndicatedUrl>
			<description><![CDATA[Featured articles are being tested. Canonical too.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p>1010 WINS Yes! In your face, Gandhi! Can we have Bender Burgers again? I didn't ask for a completely reasonable excuse! I asked you to get busy! Bender, quit destroying the universe! That could be 'my' beautiful soul sitting naked on a couch. If I could just learn to play this stupid thing.</p>
  <p>No argument here. Say it in Russian! I could if you hadn't turned on the light and shut off my stereo. Bender, we're trying our best. No! The kind with looting and maybe starting a few fires! You seem malnourished.<br /> Are you suffering from intestinal parasites?</p>
<div class="component--brightcove">
  <div class="player">
        <iframe src="https://players.brightcove.net/5757251889001/9klBjvbUGf_default/index.html?videoId=5837753158001" allowfullscreen="" webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" style="width: 640px; height: 360px;"></iframe>
  </div>
</div>

  <p>Shut up and take my money! You can see how I lived before I met you. I'll get my kit! Oh, I don't have time for this. I have to go and buy a single piece of fruit with a coupon and then return it, making people wait behind me while I complain.</p>
<div class="component--brightcove">
  <div class="player">
        <iframe src="https://players.brightcove.net/5757251889001/9klBjvbUGf_default/index.html?videoId=6042843868001" allowfullscreen="" webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" style="width: 640px; height: 360px;"></iframe>
  </div>
</div>

]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl/>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline>We&apos;re using this to test the  tag and canonical status.</subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[Canonical and Feature Testing]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://radioimg.s3.amazonaws.com/winsam/styles/nts_image_cover_tall_775x425/s3/Madonna_5_3.jpg?yDm86AOLDahtpDAErRars2NK_0zGri_W&amp;itok=PcXkt1az?width=800</coverImage>
			<featured>true</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div class="component--brightcove">
  <div class="player">
        <iframe src="https://players.brightcove.net/5757251889001/9klBjvbUGf_default/index.html?videoId=6015387059001" allowfullscreen="" webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" style="width: 640px; height: 360px;"></iframe>
  </div>
</div>

]]></lead>
			<category>Voodoo</category>
			<category>Rock</category>
			<editorialFeeds>Throwbacks</editorialFeeds>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
