<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:mi="http://schemas.ingestion.microsoft.com/common/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
	<channel>
		<title>Radio.com Reverse Chron Feed</title>
		<description>Most recent content from Radio.com</description>
		<link>https://www.radio.com</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 17:18:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
		<copyright>2019</copyright>
		<generator>Feed delivered by Clay</generator>
		<category>Lucille Ball,Hollywood,I Love Lucy,Desi Arnaz,Entertainment,Alex Trebek</category>
		<category>Fantasy Football</category>
		<category>Meghan Markle,Prince Harry,real estate</category>
		<category>Pop,Ariana Grande,Social House</category>
		<category>Nick Jonas,Jonas Brothers,Priyanka Chopra,Pop</category>
		<category>Kylie Jenner,Travis Scott,birthdays</category>
		<category>American Idol,Katy Perry,Luke Bryan,Lionel Richie,Ryan Seacrest</category>
		<category>Country,Luke Combs</category>
		<category>Ezekiel Elliott,Dallas Cowboys</category>
		<category>National News,toni morrison,Obituary,literature</category>
		<category>Lebron James,Kawhi Leonard,James Harden,Steph Curry,Kevin Durant</category>
		<category>Rock,Tool,World Premiere</category>
		<category>Robert Kraft,New England Patriots,Dallas Cowboys,Mark Wahlberg,NFL,Football,Entertainment</category>
		<category>Bachelor,Bachelorette,Bachelor In Paradise,Chelsea Roy</category>
		<category>Robinson Cano,New York Mets,All Local,Watch Sports,Breaking News</category>
		<category>Human Resources,Small Business Growth,Employee Relations,Employee Satisfaction</category>
		<category>Andrew Luck,Indianapolis Colts,Frank Reich,NFL,Football</category>
		<category>R. Kelly</category>
		<category>Slipknot,Rock</category>
		<category>Sophie Turner,Joe Jonas,Nick Jonas,Jonas Brothers,Entertainment,Game of Thrones</category>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[QA Tags Lucille Ball for 1000! A Jeopardy-Style Quiz for Her Birthday]]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/music/entertainment-news/lucille-ball-for-1000-jeopardy-style-trivia-quiz</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 17:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/music/entertainment-news/lucille-ball-for-1000-jeopardy-style-trivia-quiz</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl/>
			<description><![CDATA[Think you know your “I Love Lucy”? Only true die-hards will be able to ace this Lucille Ball quiz.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p>Today is Lucille Ball's birthday. The legendary comedian and &quot;I Love Lucy&quot; star had a long, fruitful career and was a pioneer for funny women in Hollywood.</p>
  <p>But while everyone knows Ball for her hilarious silent comedy-influenced antics, only real fanatics know will be able to ace the pop quiz we've put together about her life. Don't worry, we've formulated these ones just like <a href="https://www.radio.com/topic/jeopardy">Jeopardy</a>, everyone's preferred trivia question style. <a href="https://www.radio.com/music/inside-jeopardy-host-alex-trebeks-79th-birthday-bash">Trebek</a> would be proud.</p>
<div class="component--html-embed">
     <!--[if lte IE 10]> <div style="width: 100%; background: red; border: 1px black; padding-top: 10px; padding-bottom: 10px; color: #fff; text-align: center; font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px"> Sorry, you are using an unsupported browser. This page will not display correctly. <br /> <a href="http://www.whatbrowser.org" style="color: #fff;" target="_blank"> Please click here to upgrade to a newer browser. </a> </div> <![endif]--> <script src="https://embed-604425.secondstreetapp.com/Scripts/dist/embed.js" data-ss-embed="promotion" data-opguid="cc19b345-a742-4ed1-9051-463c7e91a41e" data-routing="hash">/**/</script> 
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl/>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline></subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[A Jeopardy-Style Lucille Ball Quiz for Her Birthday]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/GettyImages1325784-1547db34-046f-45d2-b266-e6998cd4b80a.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>false</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject" data-editable="inlinestuff">
    <div class="image-wrapper">
        
          <img src="https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/GettyImages1325784-f5c537df-41a0-44f6-aab6-952d5f95dcc3.jpg?width=800" alt="lucille ball looking glamorous in a vintage pic">
        
    </div>
      <figcaption itemprop="caption" class="image-figcaption">
        
        <cite class="credit">Photo credit Getty Images</cite>
      </figcaption>
</div>]]></lead>
			<category>Lucille Ball</category>
			<category>Hollywood</category>
			<category>I Love Lucy</category>
			<category>Desi Arnaz</category>
			<category>Entertainment</category>
			<category>Alex Trebek</category>
			<category>Flourish & Blotss</category>
			<category>"M & M Candies"</category>
			<category>“Fancieness”</category>
			<dc:creator>Eldis Sula</dc:creator>
			<editorialFeeds>Trending</editorialFeeds>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Fantasy Football Training Camp Round-Up]]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/sports/fantasy-football-training-camp-round-up</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 17:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/sports/fantasy-football-training-camp-round-up</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl></syndicatedUrl>
			<description><![CDATA[Read - Fantasy Football Training Camp Round-Up - and more NFL news and rumors on Radio.com. ]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p><strong>• Encouraging</strong></p>
  <p><strong>Lamar Jackson Firing On All Cylinders</strong></p>
  <p>The second-year signal caller has shown marked improvement throughout the offseason, according to multiple reports.</p>
  <p><strong>Fantasy Fallout</strong>: On top of the conjecture that he’ll break Cam Newton’s record for quarterback rushes, it seems Jackson’s passing game has taken a big leap. <a href="https://twitter.com/jamisonhensley/status/1158473947257556992">ESPN Ravens reporter Jamison Henley</a> tweeted that Jackson was connecting at a high rate and “throwing the ball with a lot of confidence,” while teammates Earl Thomas and Nick Boyle are <a href="https://ravenswire.usatoday.com/2019/08/04/baltimore-ravens-2019-training-camp-earl-thomas-lamar-jackson-dropping-dimes/">lauding his performance so far</a>. These reports then beg the question of whether or not Lamar Jackson can be trusted as a starting QB in fantasy. I feel much safer with a more proven signal-caller, but for those looking to take a risk, Jackson is a great choice who you can draft late and back up with someone like Philip Rivers or Kirk Cousins for a nice safety net.</p>
  <p><strong>D’Onta Foreman Waived By Texans, Signed By Colts</strong></p>
  <p>The college standout and third-round draft pick was cut by Houston in a move that caught everyone by surprise, according to <a href="https://twitter.com/McClain_on_NFL/status/1157993422415966208">John McClain of the Houston Chronicle</a>. <a href="https://twitter.com/TomPelissero/status/1158482177203605504">Tom Pelissero of NFL Network</a> then broke the news that, only a day later, the Colts scooped him up.</p>
  <p><strong>Fantasy Fallout</strong>: The winner from this? Houston RBs. <a href="https://sportsradio610.radio.com/articles/miller-says-he-feels-quicker-after-pro-bowl-season">Lamar Miller owns the Houston backfield</a> for now, and there are many young running backs on the depth chart that could see an opportunity based on camp performances. If Foreman turns his injury-wrecked career around in Indianapolis, it will a) make the Colts an unstoppable force, and b) make the Texans look really, <em>really</em> bad. For now, though, it’s hard to trust the running back who has missed nearly two seasons with a devastating Achilles tear. It wasn’t solely the injury recovery and risk that got him cut, though, as McClain noted the team cited his poor work habits as a factor in the decision. Additionally, while Marlon Mack should be the lead in Indy, training camp should help to push someone to the front of the backup race, be it Foreman, Nyheim Heins, or Jordan Wilkins.</p>
  <p><strong>TJ Hockenson Impressing With Hands</strong></p>
  <p>The first-round pick from this year’s draft has “linked up with Matthew Stafford for a number of touchdowns,” per <a href="https://971theticket.radio.com/articles/great-thing-about-tj-hockenson-has-impressed-matt-patricia">Will Burchfield of 97.1 The Ticket</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Fantasy Fallout</strong>: With the scarcity of dependable tight ends, it’s encouraging to see that head coach Matt Patricia has praised the rookie’s consistency. Though Stafford usually hasn’t leaned on his tight end, Hockensen is a talent that they took very early- eighth overall, as a matter of fact- and want to use right away. He’s not even being taken in all drafts, so you can take him late as a backup TE and wait to see if something develops.</p>
  <p><strong>• Concerning</strong></p>
<div itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject" data-editable="inlinestuff">
    <div class="image-wrapper">
        
          <img src="https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/GettyImages1068912366-622a55ec-6afd-4742-bf4d-58ec75f11633.jpg?width=800" alt="Melvin Gordon is holding out. ">
        
    </div>
      <figcaption itemprop="caption" class="image-figcaption">
        <span class="caption">Melvin Gordon is holding out.</span>
        <cite class="credit">Photo credit (Harry How/Getty Images)</cite>
      </figcaption>
</div>  <p><strong>Chargers Staying Put, Gordon Requesting Trade</strong></p>
  <p>The Chargers emphasized their $10 million per year offer, and Gordon still won’t budge, according to <a href="https://twitter.com/SportsCenter/status/1156962846460338176">ESPN’s Josina Anderson</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Fantasy Fallout</strong>: Anderson also noted that general manager “Tom Telesco denied permission for Gordon to seek trade partners,” making the sticky situation even stickier. You can’t spend a first-round pick on Gordon right now. You just can’t. There are safer, if less flattering, options on the board, and any production is better than the potential for no production, especially with your most important fantasy asset. Wait and see <a href="https://www.radio.com/sports/nfl/melvin-gordons-agent-says-he-requested-trade-from-chargers">how this story develops</a>, and expect Austin Ekeler and Justin Jackson to keep trending up.</p>
  <p><strong>Packers RBs Dealing With Hamstring Issues</strong></p>
  <p>Head coach Matt LaFleur is opting to keep starter Aaron Jones and backup Jamaal Williams out of practice for now, says that the Packers are taking a cautious approach to their running backs’ health (via <a href="https://www.packersnews.com/story/sports/nfl/packers/2019/07/31/green-bay-packers-notes-darnell-savage-set-ease-into-training-camp/1878985001/">Ryan Wood and Jim Owczarski of Packers News</a>).</p>
  <p><strong>Fantasy Fallout</strong>: Both Jones and Williams are<a href="https://wgr550.radio.com/articles/opinion/five-tricky-fantasy-running-back-situations"> risky but draft-worthy backs</a>, and the Packers’ concern with their health just means that they know how important they are to the team’s success on offense. Jones broke out in a big way last season, recording double-digit fantasy totals in seven of his 11 full games last year. <em>Full</em> is a keyword there, as he missed time due to injury and has not yet recorded a fully healthy season. If he does, his third-round ADP will be well-worth it, but hamstring issues in the offseason might point to the trend continuing throughout 2019. Williams is a must-have handcuff if you draft Jones, as you can wait until the end of the draft to take him and he had a pair of 15-plus point games in Jones’ absence last season.</p>
  <p><strong>Andrew Luck, Colts Weapons Continue to be Limited in OTAs</strong></p>
  <p>The star quarterback who enjoyed a fantastic comeback season last year is dealing with nagging calf issues, according to multiple reports from <a href="https://twitter.com/zkeefer">Zak Keefer of The Athletic</a>. Additionally, Parris Campbell, Devin Funchess, and Jack Doyle have all experienced health issues of some sort.</p>
  <p><strong>Fantasy Fallout</strong>: The most encouraging of these reports from Keefer says that there is no reason to panic about Luck and that the team is just making sure he gets to full health. However, a calf injury that has lasted this long is definitely cause for concern until we get confirmation that <a href="https://www.radio.com/sports/nfl/andrew-luck-i-certainly-expect-to-play-week-1">he’ll play normally come Week 1</a>. Campbell has not practiced yet due to a hamstring injury, Doyle is still working to recover his oblique, and Funchess came up limping in Sunday’s practice. Keep an eye on all of them, but none of these seem like they’re too major.</p>
  <p><strong>Damien Williams Missing Time, Frustrating Andy Reid</strong></p>
  <p><a href="https://twitter.com/adamteicher/status/1157701754202599424">ESPN’s Adam Teicher</a> noted the frustration in Reid’s voice as he discussed Williams and the hamstring injury that’s keeping him out of practice.</p>
  <p><strong>Fantasy Fallout</strong>: A <a href="https://www.radio.com/sports/fantasy-football-5-running-back-busts-to-avoid-drafting">potential bust candidate</a> for 2019, Williams has allowed opportunities for the other Kansas City backs, like Carlos Hyde, Darwin Thompson, Darrell Williams, and <a href="https://www.chiefs.com/news/five-things-we-learned-at-chiefs-training-camp-on-sunday">cornerback-turned-running back Tremon Smith</a>. Hyde seems to be the guy to draft out of this bunch, but as we’ve seen in past seasons, the Chiefs can roll out pretty much anyone and they’ll have success. If Williams can return to the field at some point soon, you can resume drafting him as a risky RB1 or RB2, but there is uncertainty in the air surrounding one of last year’s biggest surprises.</p>
  <p><strong>• Draft As Usual</strong></p>
<div itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject" data-editable="inlinestuff">
    <div class="image-wrapper">
        
          <img src="https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/GettyImages1090319914-75dd909b-b289-4e97-a084-98a5d3316a9a.jpg?width=800" alt="Amari Cooper had a big second-half with the Cowboys in 2018. ">
        
    </div>
      <figcaption itemprop="caption" class="image-figcaption">
        <span class="caption">Amari Cooper had a big second-half with the Cowboys in 2018.</span>
        <cite class="credit">Photo credit (Ronald Martinez/Getty Images)</cite>
      </figcaption>
</div>  <p><strong>Cowboys Careful With Amari Cooper After Minor Injury</strong></p>
  <p>After Cooper injured his heel in Friday’s practice, <a href="https://1053thefan.radio.com/articles/news/cowboys-camp-amari-cooper-sidelined-heel-bruise">he was pulled early on Saturday</a>.</p>
  <p>Fantasy Fallout: Expect the Cowboys to exercise caution with preserving Cooper, who clicked with quarterback Dak Prescott right away last season and adds a whole new dimension to the Dallas offense that was desperately needed. However, a bruised heel is not typically an injury that lingers more than a couple weeks, and could be played through if need be. Luckily, Cooper doesn’t <em>need </em>to play in the preseason, and will likely be kept extremely limited in game action until the regular season rolls around. This shouldn’t change where he’s drafted at all, obviously barring any setbacks, and Cooper is worth a pick as a back-end WR1.</p>
  <p><strong>Andy Isabella Suffers Minor Knee Injury</strong></p>
  <p>The highly-touted rookie receiver will be questionable for Arizona’s first preseason game, according to head coach Kliff Kingsbury at a press conference.</p>
  <p><strong>Fantasy Fallout</strong>: Isabella was taken in the second round by the Cardinals, an intriguing team from a fantasy standpoint. It’s largely dependent on how quarterback Kyler Murray fits into Kliff Kingsbury’s scheme, but. One thing is easier to predict, though- the Cardinals will not be a very good team on the defensive side of the ball, and will probably be throwing a lot. Pro Football Focus ranked the Cardinals’ roster as the worst in football heading into 2019, and this game script should play out well in fantasy value. This means that, though Isabella is behind Fitzgerald and Kirk in the corps, there is a good opportunity for a solid target count. You don’t need to spend a valuable pick on him, so wait until later on and stash him as a sleeper candidate.</p>
  <p><strong>Ezekiel Elliott Standing Strong</strong></p>
  <p><a href="https://twitter.com/JosinaAnderson/status/1158727938151522304?s=20">ESPN’s Josina Anderson</a> reported that the centerpiece of the Dallas offense threatens to hold out the 2019 season without a new contract.</p>
  <p><strong>Fantasy Fallout</strong>: She also notes that this is unlikely given that “Jerry Jones wants to get a deal done.” But still, there are hints of Le’Veon Bell in the air, and this is just another reason to wait as long as possible before getting to that fantasy draft. That said, if you already drafted him, it seems you can breathe easy. The Cowboys need Zeke, and they have built their entire team around his otherworldly talent. We’ll know by the end of the preseason, and perhaps a lot sooner, what happens with Dallas’s brightest star.</p>
  <p><strong>Tom Brady Earns Extension</strong></p>
  <p><a href="https://twitter.com/RapSheet/status/1158073982173634561">NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport</a> reported that the two parties agreed on a two-year deal worth $70 million, marking the first time in Brady’s career that he’s earned more than $20 million in a season.</p>
  <p><strong>Fantasy Fallout</strong>: None. Brady will remain with the Patriots as thought, but the <a href="https://weei.radio.com/blogs/andy-hart/patriots-quarterback-tom-bradys-extension-creates-questions-future-uncertainty">extension is a little bit deceptive</a> as Rapoport notes that “it’s essentially year-to-year.” Brady had one of his least-productive fantasy seasons in 2018, and the Patriots still won the Super Bowl. They can win in a number of ways, and passing less might be that formula now, establishing Brady’s ranking as a backup fantasy quarterback. ESPN’s Adam Schefter appeared on <a href="https://weei.radio.com/blogs/ryan-hannable/espns-adam-schefter-gives-updates-tom-brady-rob-gronkowski-josh-gordon">WEEI</a> to discuss the trade further.</p>
  <p><strong>Trey Burton (Groin) Misses Several Practices</strong></p>
  <p>Tuesday marked the fourth-straight practice missed by the veteran tight end, according to <a href="https://twitter.com/BradBiggs/status/1158736616468418560">Brad Biggs of the Chicago Tribune</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Fantasy Fallout</strong>: Burton was decent last year, and that’s enough to make it as a TE1 in fantasy football. He scored a pretty underwhelming 93.1 points last year, and finished as the sixth-best tight end. While his current prolonged absence is a little disconcerting, it’s still early in camp, and Biggs noted that <a href="https://670thescore.radio.com/chicago-bears-trey-burton-sidelined-practice-riley-ridley-injury-updates">Nagy just wants to be “smart with the veteran.”</a> The sixth-year tight end will probably come close to replicating last year’s stats if healthy, but that doesn’t mean he’ll finish in the same place in the rankings. Don’t rush to grab Burton if you miss out on the top tier, as many players will produce at a similar level.</p>
  <p><strong>Antonio Brown’s Feet Keep Him Out Of Camp</strong></p>
  <p>The star has missed time early on with his new team with badly “blistered feet,” according to <a href="https://twitter.com/bylindsayhjones/status/1157386177277599746">Lindsay Jones of The Athletic</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Fantasy Fallout</strong>: What an interesting injury designation that would be. There should be no reason for concern, though, other than that Brown is getting less time to mesh with his new quarterback. There’s no foreseeable way that this issue should last long at all, and a quick pedicure should do the trick. After the departure of both Amari Cooper and Jared Cook, Brown could have the highest target count in the entire league in a system that will likely air out the ball often. Draft him as a WR1 somewhere after the elite tier of DeAndre Hopkins, Julio Jones, and Davante Adams.</p>
  <p><strong>Unexpected QB Atop Redskins Depth Chart</strong></p>
  <p>Colt McCoy leads the depth chart at quarterback, followed by Case Keenum at No. 2 and previously expected-starter Dwayne Haskins at No. 3 (<a href="https://thefandc.radio.com/redskins-release-first-unofficial-depth-chart">via Ben Krimmel at 106.7 The Fan</a>).</p>
  <p><strong>Fantasy Fallout</strong>: Yikes. All this spells for me is to stay away from Washington. With Haskins there was a <em>little </em>bit of intrigue, but McCoy’s career just doesn’t seem to lead to fantasy production, and at age 33, it doesn’t seem like a sudden turnaround is in store. Obviously this depth chart isn’t set in stone, but regardless of the situation, the Redskins might just be the worst team for fantasy football talent.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl></stationUrl>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline></subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[Fantasy Football Training Camp Round-Up]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/GettyImages1078758304-f3473afe-7b07-404e-be56-6bc55d988471.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured></featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject" data-editable="inlinestuff">
    <div class="image-wrapper">
        
          <img src="https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/GettyImages1078758304-86bc7770-502b-4821-a51b-de55ee713978.jpg?width=800" alt="2019 will be Lamar Jackson&#x27;s first full season as a starter. (Patrick Smith/Getty Images)">
        
    </div>
      <figcaption itemprop="caption" class="image-figcaption">
        <span class="caption">2019 will be Lamar Jackson's first full season as a starter. (Patrick Smith/Getty Images)</span>
        
      </figcaption>
</div>]]></lead>
			<category>Fantasy Football</category>
			<dc:creator>Jordan Cohn</dc:creator>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Meghan Markle's LA Home Can Be Yours for $1.8 Million]]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/music/entertainment-news/meghan-markles-la-home-can-be-yours-for-usd1-8-million</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 16:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/music/entertainment-news/meghan-markles-la-home-can-be-yours-for-usd1-8-million</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl/>
			<description><![CDATA[See photos of Meghan Markle’s beautiful LA home that she lived in for two years before moving to Kensington Palace with Prince Harry. Markle now lives in Frogmore Cottage. ]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p>Meghan Markle may be living the royal life across the pond, but she’s still got some affairs to deal with stateside. Markle’s Los Angeles home is on the market for $1.8 million.</p>
  <p>The home is a beautiful four-bedroom, three-bathroom colonial-style with a white exterior, <a href="https://www.homes.com/blog/2019/08/meghan-markles-la-home-for-sale/">Homes.com outlines</a>. And while it’s much cozier than Markle’s Frogmore Cottage situation, the home is very spacious with tons of natural light and is “perfect for entertaining.”</p>
<aside class="component--tweet">
  <blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Live like the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/RoyalFamily?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#RoyalFamily</a>! <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/MeghanMarkle?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#MeghanMarkle</a>&#39;s Los Angeles home is up for sale. Are(chie) you ready to move in? I know we are. <a href="https://t.co/FeskIoL3Ax">https://t.co/FeskIoL3Ax</a> <a href="https://t.co/nwJpT0wPwh">pic.twitter.com/nwJpT0wPwh</a></p>&mdash; Homes.com (@HomesDotCom) <a href="https://twitter.com/HomesDotCom/status/1158467855181942784?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 5, 2019</a></blockquote>

</aside>
  <p>Much of the house is white with black accents, and if the beautifully staged rooms weren’t enough of a selling point, the fact that <a href="https://www.radio.com/music/entertainment-news/gallery/happy-birthday-meghan-markle-9-times-her-fashion-was-fabulous">it was fit for a current royal </a>should be. It’s 2,262 square feet of “home décor inspo,”<a href="https://www.cosmopolitan.com/entertainment/celebs/a28613751/meghan-markle-los-angeles-home-for-sale-pictures-listing/">Cosmpolitan reports.</a></p>
  <p>Markle was able to enjoy an open floor plan, fireplace, Jack and Jill style bathrooms, and all of those windows for two years before moving to the palace with Harry. Who knew so many accent pillows were such a good thing?</p>
  <p>But it’s time for Markle to do away with all of the windows and got herself a little more privacy for her life as a royal. Markle and Prince Harry married in 2018 and recently <a href="https://www.radio.com/music/entertainment-news/meghan-markle-got-parenting-advice-from-michelle-obama">welcomed their first child, Archie,</a> into the world on May 6thof this year.</p>
  <p>Markle has been living full-time in Windsor, England since 2018.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl/>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline></subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[Meghan Markle's LA Home Can Be Yours for $1.8 Million]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/MeghanMarkle3-3987ed00-c6e0-4009-80b2-0685366d2e7d.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>false</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div class="component--brightcove">
  <div class="player">
        <iframe src="https://players.brightcove.net/5757251889001/9klBjvbUGf_default/index.html?videoId=6067492501001" allowfullscreen="" webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" style="width: 640px; height: 360px;"></iframe>
  </div>
</div>
]]></lead>
			<category>Meghan Markle</category>
			<category>Prince Harry</category>
			<category>real estate</category>
			<dc:creator>Jacquie Cadorette</dc:creator>
			<editorialFeeds>Trending</editorialFeeds>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Is Ariana Grande Dating Mikey Foster of Social House?]]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/music/pop/is-ariana-grande-dating-mikey-foster-of-social-house</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 16:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/music/pop/is-ariana-grande-dating-mikey-foster-of-social-house</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl/>
			<description><![CDATA[The “boyfriend” collaborators have been spotted out together.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p>“But we be so smitten it’s crazy”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.usmagazine.com/celebrity-news/news/ariana-grande-holds-hands-with-mikey-foster-during-night-out/">US Weekly</a> reports that <strong>Ariana Grande</strong> has made the most of her trip to Chicago for Lollapalooza. The <em>Sweetener</em> singer has been spotted out at the same Italian restaurant twice, both times appearing very close with <strong>Social House</strong> singer <strong>Mikey Foster</strong>.</p>
  <p>According to <a href="https://www.usmagazine.com/celebrity-news/news/ariana-grande-holds-hands-with-mikey-foster-during-night-out/">US Weekly</a>, the two arrived separately to Siena Tavern, but sources claim they were seen “holding hands.”</p>
<aside class="component--instagram-post">
  <blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/p/B0zDQmGFW6Y/" data-instgrm-version="12" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"><div style="padding:16px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B0zDQmGFW6Y/" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"> <div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"></div></div></div><div style="padding: 19% 0;"></div> <div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"><svg width="50px" height="50px" viewBox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"><g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"><g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"><g><path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"></path></g></g></g></svg></div><div style="padding-top: 8px;"> <div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"> View this post on Instagram</div></div><div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"><div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"></div></div><div style="margin-left: 8px;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"></div></div><div style="margin-left: auto;"> <div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"></div></div></div></a> <p style=" margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B0zDQmGFW6Y/" style=" color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;" target="_blank">♡</a></p> <p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;">A post shared by <a href="https://www.instagram.com/arianagrande/" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px;" target="_blank"> Ariana Grande</a> (@arianagrande) on <time style=" font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;" datetime="2019-08-05T21:38:29+00:00">Aug 5, 2019 at 2:38pm PDT</time></p></div></blockquote>
</aside>
<aside class="component--instagram-post">
  <blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/p/B0ytjixFITd/" data-instgrm-version="12" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"><div style="padding:16px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B0ytjixFITd/" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"> <div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"></div></div></div><div style="padding: 19% 0;"></div> <div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"><svg width="50px" height="50px" viewBox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"><g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"><g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"><g><path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"></path></g></g></g></svg></div><div style="padding-top: 8px;"> <div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"> View this post on Instagram</div></div><div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"><div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"></div></div><div style="margin-left: 8px;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"></div></div><div style="margin-left: auto;"> <div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"></div></div></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center; margin-bottom: 24px;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 224px;"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 144px;"></div></div></a><p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B0ytjixFITd/" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none;" target="_blank">A post shared by Ariana Grande (@arianagrande)</a> on <time style=" font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;" datetime="2019-08-05T18:28:50+00:00">Aug 5, 2019 at 11:28am PDT</time></p></div></blockquote>
</aside>
  <p>Foster and his Social House partner <strong>Scootie Anderson</strong> have been longtime collaborators with Grande, helping to write and produce several songs on the star’s last album, including “7 rings” and “thank u, next.” Last week they stepped into the spotlight, joining Grande on her new song, “boyfriend.”</p>
  <p>Grande also released a look at the making of her “boyfriend” video on Monday. “My mom, I have to ask her to leave” she smiles as they discuss the pair’s make out scene for the video. “I begged her to come here. I told her it would be so fun.”</p>
<div class="component--html-embed">
    <div class="html-embed__iframe-container">
      <div class="iframe-container__padded-container">
        <iframe width="788" height="454" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/adUEoX6dXlc" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
      </div>
    </div>
</div>
  <p>In addition to working behind-the-scenes with Ariana, Social House have been serving as the opening act for her <em>Sweetener World Tour</em>.</p>
  <p>Before the release of “boyfriend”, Grande shed some light on the song which she sings with Foster.</p>
  <p>“People want to feel love but don’t want to define their relationship, and have trouble fully committing or trusting or allowing themselves to fully love someone, even though they want to” she wrote on Twitter. “We wanted to make something uplifting that captures that feeling of being afraid to take the leap and trust, being afraid of being hurt or feeling like you won’t be enough for that person, but also how it feels to have a crippling crush on someone.”</p>
  <p><strong>WATCH MORE</strong>: <a href="https://www.radio.com/blogs/michael-cerio/social-house-takes-us-back-day-they-created-7-rings-ariana-grande">Social House Takes Us Back to the Day They Created &quot;7 Rings&quot; With Ariana Grande</a></p>
<div class="component--brightcove">
  <div class="player">
        <iframe src="https://players.brightcove.net/5757251889001/9klBjvbUGf_default/index.html?videoId=6036721161001" allowfullscreen="" webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" style="width: 640px; height: 360px;"></iframe>
  </div>
</div>
  <p>Both Grande and Foster will be heading to Europe later this month to continue the <em>Sweetener World Tour</em>. You can find the full list of dates <a href="https://www.arianagrande.com/events">here</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl/>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline>The “boyfriend” collaborators have been spotted holding hands</subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[Is Ariana Grande Dating Mikey Foster of Social House?]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/ArianaSocialHouse-66c19035-9c0d-4844-b708-7e338a769baf.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>false</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject" data-editable="inlinestuff">
    <div class="image-wrapper">
        
          <img src="https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/ArianaSocialHouse-7cac2f94-c8fb-46b1-8918-936413546f9c.jpg?width=800" alt="Ariana Grande and Mikey Foster of Social House">
        
    </div>
      <figcaption itemprop="caption" class="image-figcaption">
        
        <cite class="credit">Photo credit <a href="https://www.gettyimages.com/search/photographer?family=editorial&amp;photographer=Mike+Coppola">Mike Coppola</a> / Staff</cite>
      </figcaption>
</div>]]></lead>
			<category>Pop</category>
			<category>Ariana Grande</category>
			<category>Social House</category>
			<dc:creator>Michael Cerio</dc:creator>
			<editorialFeeds>Hot AC / Top 40 / CHR</editorialFeeds>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Nick Jonas Sells Beverly Hills Bachelor Pad for $6.9 Million]]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/music/pop/nick-jonas-sells-beverly-hills-bachelor-pad-for-usd6-9-million</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 16:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/music/pop/nick-jonas-sells-beverly-hills-bachelor-pad-for-usd6-9-million</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl/>
			<description><![CDATA[Nick Jonas Sells Beverly Hills Bachelor Pad for $6.9 Million]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p>A ring is one thing, but selling your bachelor pad is the true sign of commitment. <strong>Nick Jonas</strong> unloaded his airy Beverly Hills home in order to search for something with new bride <strong>Priyanka Chopra</strong>.</p>
  <p>Sources told <a href="https://www.tmz.com/2019/08/06/nick-jonas-sells-bachelor-pad-los-angeles-bigger-home-priyanka-chopra/">TMZ</a> Nicks’s 4,129 square foot abode in the hills above LA sold for $6.9 million, after he paid $6.5 million only about a year ago.</p>
<aside class="component--tweet">
  <blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Nick Jonas Sells Bachelor Pad, Looking with Priyanka For Gigantic Mansion <a href="https://t.co/QBJmK7rOdN">https://t.co/QBJmK7rOdN</a></p>&mdash; TMZ (@TMZ) <a href="https://twitter.com/TMZ/status/1158646801295011841?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 6, 2019</a></blockquote>

</aside>
  <p>Jonas is leaving behind five bedrooms and five baths and an “elevated clerestory roof that ushers in light while framing expansive views of the canyon beyond.” Other highlights include a floating guest wing and extended wood terrace that surround a pool.</p>
  <p>A source told TMZ Nick and Priyanka are now on the hunt for something in the $20 million dollar range in Beverly Hills or nearby Bel-Air.</p>
  <p>If the happy couple hasn’t found anything yet, the search is about to become interrupted. The <strong>Jonas Brothers</strong> <em>Happiness Tour</em> begins this week in Miami and runs all the way to December 15 before a break. Get the full schedule <a href="https://jonasbrothers.com/tour/">here</a>.</p>
  <p>The band is back together with their first studio album in a decade. <em>Happiness Begins</em> features the hit singles “Sucker,” “Cool” and “Only Human.”</p>
<div class="component--html-embed">
    <div class="html-embed__iframe-container">
      <div class="iframe-container__padded-container">
        <iframe src="//players.brightcove.net/5757251889001/SkXmVqJHX_default/index.html?videoId=6031887647001"
allowfullscreen
webkitallowfullscreen
mozallowfullscreen
allow="encrypted-media"
width="300"
height="150"></iframe>

      </div>
    </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl/>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline>The newly-married man is looking for an upgrade</subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[Nick Jonas Sells Beverly Hills Bachelor Pad for $6.9 Million]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/NickJonas-08c8ec2a-1754-4a3d-8668-b6fb415e0b05.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>false</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject" data-editable="inlinestuff">
    <div class="image-wrapper">
        
          <img src="https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/NickJonas-dd3dd9b0-20e9-47f0-b400-d7da4bdd7292.jpg?width=800" alt="Nick Jonas from the Jonas Brothers on stage during Capital&#x27;s Summertime Ball.">
        
    </div>
      <figcaption itemprop="caption" class="image-figcaption">
        <span class="caption">Nick Jonas</span>
        <cite class="credit">Photo credit © Press Association</cite>
      </figcaption>
</div>]]></lead>
			<category>Nick Jonas</category>
			<category>Jonas Brothers</category>
			<category>Priyanka Chopra</category>
			<category>Pop</category>
			<dc:creator>Bob Diehl</dc:creator>
			<editorialFeeds>AC</editorialFeeds>
			<editorialFeeds>Hot AC / Top 40 / CHR</editorialFeeds>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[See Travis Scott’s Totally Romantic Surprise for Kylie Jenner’s Birthday]]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/music/entertainment-news/travis-scotts-romantic-surprise-for-kylie-jenners-birthday</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 15:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/music/entertainment-news/travis-scotts-romantic-surprise-for-kylie-jenners-birthday</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl/>
			<description><![CDATA[See how Travis Scott has kicked off Kylie Jenner’s birthday week with a romantic surprise. ]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p>Travis Scott is making <a href="https://www.radio.com/music/entertainment-news/these-are-instagrams-top-earners">Kylie Jenner’s</a> cleaning staff work overtime.</p>
  <p>The rapper gave the “Keeping Up with the Kardashians” star an early birthday gift by surprising her with thousands of rose petals scattered all over the floor of her home, according to <a href="https://pagesix.com/2019/08/05/travis-scott-fills-kylie-jenners-home-with-roses-for-her-birthday/">Page Six.</a></p>
  <p>The Lip Kit maven shared video of the overindulgent gesture on Instagram.</p>
<div class="component--html-embed">
    <blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/p/B0y8EmenMGM/" data-instgrm-version="12" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:540px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"><div style="padding:16px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B0y8EmenMGM/" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"> <div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"></div></div></div><div style="padding: 19% 0;"></div> <div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"><svg width="50px" height="50px" viewBox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"><g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"><g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"><g><path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"></path></g></g></g></svg></div><div style="padding-top: 8px;"> <div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"> View this post on Instagram</div></div><div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"><div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"></div></div><div style="margin-left: 8px;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"></div></div><div style="margin-left: auto;"> <div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"></div></div></div></a> <p style=" margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B0y8EmenMGM/" style=" color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;" target="_blank">My house is covered in ROSES! @travisscott and it’s not even my birthday yet!!!!! Omg ♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️😭😭😭😭</a></p> <p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;">A post shared by <a href="https://www.instagram.com/kyliejenner/" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px;" target="_blank"> Kylie ✨</a> (@kyliejenner) on <time style=" font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;" datetime="2019-08-05T20:37:12+00:00">Aug 5, 2019 at 1:37pm PDT</time></p></div></blockquote> <script async src="//www.instagram.com/embed.js"></script>
</div>
  <p>“My house is covered in ROSES! <a href="https://www.instagram.com/travisscott/">@travisscott</a> and it’s not even my birthday yet!!!!!,” Jenner captioned the clip that shows her feet walking through the massive deluge of red petals as her daughter Stormi throws some in the air.  Condolences to whomever has to sweep all that up!</p>
  <p>The reality star also flashed the birthday card Scott gave her, which said, “Happy Birthday!!!! We’re just getting started. Love you!!!!”</p>
  <p>Kylie doesn’t turn 22 until August 10<sup>th</sup>, so who knows what other extravagant gifts the “Sicko Mode” singer has in store for his “wifey.”</p>
  <p>Last year, Scott notoriously gifted the mother of his child a vintage 1950s Rolls Royce for her 21st birthday. The vehicle was estimated to be worth between $25 thousand and $85 thousand.</p>
  <p>It’s also been <a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/kylie-jenner-rented-most-extravagant-182900012.html">reported</a> that Jenner has rented a $250 million luxury yacht that’s the size of a football field to celebrate her birthday.</p>
  <p>The ship is called Tranquility and accommodates 22 guests (<a href="https://www.radio.com/music/entertainment-news/khloe-kardashian-considers-reconciling-with-jordyn-woods">but probably not Jordyn Woods</a>) in 10 cabins and features a helipad, beauty salon, swimming pool and a jacuzzi. All the basic necessities!</p>
  <p>In addition, the yacht comes with a 29-person crew and will allegedly make multiple stops along the Mediterranean Sea.</p>
  <p>Party like you’re the <a href="https://www.radio.com/articles/kylie-jenner-youngest-self-made-billionaire-according-forbes">world’s youngest self-made billionaire</a>!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl/>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline></subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[Travis Scott’s Romantic Surprise for Kylie Jenner’s Birthday]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/TravisScottKylieJenner-bb68eead-1183-4b6c-8bad-e7c34e078d49.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>false</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div class="component--brightcove">
  <div class="player">
        <iframe src="https://players.brightcove.net/5757251889001/9klBjvbUGf_default/index.html?videoId=6031871506001" allowfullscreen="" webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" style="width: 640px; height: 360px;"></iframe>
  </div>
</div>
]]></lead>
			<category>Kylie Jenner</category>
			<category>Travis Scott</category>
			<category>birthdays</category>
			<dc:creator>Johnny Lopez</dc:creator>
			<editorialFeeds>Trending</editorialFeeds>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Katy Perry, Luke Bryan, Lionel Richie Officially Returning to 'American Idol']]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/music/entertainment-news/katy-luke-lionel-officially-returning-to-american-idol</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 15:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/music/entertainment-news/katy-luke-lionel-officially-returning-to-american-idol</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl/>
			<description><![CDATA[Katy Perry, Luke Bryan, Lionel Richie Officially Returning to ‘American Idol’]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p>The gang is getting back together. <strong>Katy Perry</strong>, <strong>Luke Bryan </strong>and <strong>Lionel Richie</strong> have all officially signed on for the next season of “American Idol.”</p>
  <p>Auditions had already been underway, but it wasn’t a done deal that the trio of stars would be back as judges. <strong>Bobby Bones</strong> is also returning as in-house mentor.</p>
  <p>“We couldn’t be more excited for Katy, Luke, Lionel and Bobby to continue in their roles as American Idol searches for the next great music star, with more live episodes and exciting, new creative elements coming this season.” Said ABC Entertainment president <strong>Karey Burke</strong>.</p>
  <p>The three judges all tweeted their excitement about their reunion.</p>
<aside class="component--tweet">
  <blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">IT’S OFFICIAL, 3RD SEASON’S A CHARM! Excited to get the band back together with <a href="https://twitter.com/LionelRichie?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@LionelRichie</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/LukeBryanOnline?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@LukeBryanOnline</a> 🙌🏼 Get out there and audition y’all! 3rd season could be your charm✨<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AmericanIdol?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#AmericanIdol</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/TheNextIdol?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#TheNextIdol</a> <a href="https://t.co/r0n6vVMrbH">pic.twitter.com/r0n6vVMrbH</a></p>&mdash; KATY PERRY (@katyperry) <a href="https://twitter.com/katyperry/status/1158408706641371136?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 5, 2019</a></blockquote>

</aside>
<aside class="component--tweet">
  <blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">The trio is getting back together! Ready for another season of laughs, tears and wigs flying on <a href="https://twitter.com/AmericanIdol?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@AmericanIdol</a>. Get out there and audition! You never know, <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/TheNextIdol?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#TheNextIdol</a> could be you... <a href="https://t.co/TNwHZNrcRV">pic.twitter.com/TNwHZNrcRV</a></p>&mdash; Luke Bryan (@LukeBryanOnline) <a href="https://twitter.com/LukeBryanOnline/status/1158409323057430539?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 5, 2019</a></blockquote>

</aside>
<aside class="component--tweet">
  <blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">New season, let’s go! So excited to be heading back to <a href="https://twitter.com/AmericanIdol?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@AmericanIdol</a> along side <a href="https://twitter.com/katyperry?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@KatyPerry</a> &amp; <a href="https://twitter.com/LukeBryanOnline?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@LukeBryanOnline</a>! Time to find another superstar! 🌟<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/TheNextIdol?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#TheNextIdol</a> <a href="https://t.co/DDFw9559Fx">pic.twitter.com/DDFw9559Fx</a></p>&mdash; Lionel Richie (@LionelRichie) <a href="https://twitter.com/LionelRichie/status/1158407564947808259?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 5, 2019</a></blockquote>

</aside>
  <p>Financial terms have not been disclosed, but Perry made an astounding $25 million her first time around.</p>
  <p>Host <strong>Ryan Seacrest</strong> is not yet signed, but Burke seems to be treating negotiations as a formality.</p>
  <p>&quot;I do not believe he will be missing,&quot; she said. &quot;We're in ongoing conversations with Ryan about returning, and I'm hopeful that he will.&quot;</p>
  <p>The 18th season of “American Idol” will air in 2020. Auditions continue in cities across America.</p>
<aside class="component--tweet">
  <blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Wanna audition to be <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/TheNextIdol?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#TheNextIdol</a>? Check out the latest list of audition cities and venues at <a href="https://t.co/2ruYWenEgA">https://t.co/2ruYWenEgA</a>! <a href="https://t.co/zMqbtE8CM3">pic.twitter.com/zMqbtE8CM3</a></p>&mdash; American Idol (@AmericanIdol) <a href="https://twitter.com/AmericanIdol/status/1158422979585249280?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 5, 2019</a></blockquote>

</aside>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl/>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline>But what about Ryan Seacrest?</subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[Katy, Luke, Lionel Officially Returning to 'American Idol']]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/AmericanIdol-e486869b-5752-40dd-bec3-1d028cdb25e7.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>false</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject" data-editable="inlinestuff">
    <div class="image-wrapper">
        
          <img src="https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/AmericanIdol-8169ea18-3ff3-43de-bad1-00bc9f6d63a8.jpg?width=800" alt="Lionel Richie, Katy Perry and Luke Bryan attend ABC&#x27;s &quot;American Idol&quot; Finale on May 19, 2019">
        
    </div>
      <figcaption itemprop="caption" class="image-figcaption">
        <span class="caption">Lionel Richie, Katy Perry, Luke Bryan</span>
        <cite class="credit">Photo credit Amy Sussman/Getty Images</cite>
      </figcaption>
</div>]]></lead>
			<category>American Idol</category>
			<category>Katy Perry</category>
			<category>Luke Bryan</category>
			<category>Lionel Richie</category>
			<category>Ryan Seacrest</category>
			<dc:creator>Bob Diehl</dc:creator>
			<editorialFeeds>AC</editorialFeeds>
			<editorialFeeds>Country</editorialFeeds>
			<editorialFeeds>Hot AC / Top 40 / CHR</editorialFeeds>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Toddler Sings 'Beer Never Broke My Heart,' Luke Combs Is Impressed!]]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/music/country/toddler-sings-beer-never-broke-my-heart-by-luke-combs</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 15:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/music/country/toddler-sings-beer-never-broke-my-heart-by-luke-combs</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl/>
			<description><![CDATA[Toddler Sings ‘Beer Never Broke My Heart,’ Luke Combs Is Impressed!]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p>He doesn’t really have any way of knowing what it means, but the emotion in which a toddler sings “Beer Never Broke My Heart” leaves you wondering.</p>
  <p><strong>Luke Combs</strong> shared a video of an unidentified boy singing his number one hit. The little guy strums a mini-acoustic guitar while singing “Long-neck ice-cold beer never broke my heart.” He sings it with the heaviest, most earnest draw imaginable, and just for effect, there’s a toy spider sitting on the kitchen floor right by his feet.</p>
  <p>Combs was impressed. He wrote: “Sing it buddy! Watch out for that spider though!!”</p>
<aside class="component--instagram-post">
  <blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/p/B0zdPW9FQM0/" data-instgrm-version="12" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"><div style="padding:16px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B0zdPW9FQM0/" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"> <div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"></div></div></div><div style="padding: 19% 0;"></div> <div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"><svg width="50px" height="50px" viewBox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"><g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"><g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"><g><path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"></path></g></g></g></svg></div><div style="padding-top: 8px;"> <div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"> View this post on Instagram</div></div><div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"><div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"></div></div><div style="margin-left: 8px;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"></div></div><div style="margin-left: auto;"> <div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"></div></div></div></a> <p style=" margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B0zdPW9FQM0/" style=" color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;" target="_blank">Sing it buddy! Watch out for that spider though!!</a></p> <p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;">A post shared by <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lukecombs/" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px;" target="_blank"> Luke Combs 🎤</a> (@lukecombs) on <time style=" font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;" datetime="2019-08-06T01:25:36+00:00">Aug 5, 2019 at 6:25pm PDT</time></p></div></blockquote>
</aside>
  <p>Other country music stars took notice too. <strong>Old Dominion</strong> called it the best video ever and <strong>Thomas Rhett</strong> said it was absolutely amazing. <strong>Dan Smyers</strong> of <strong>Dan + Shay </strong>and <strong>Mitchell Tenpenny</strong> also chimed in.</p>
  <p>“Beer Never Broke My Heart” appears on Combs’ <em>Prequel</em> EP and is his sixth straight number one song. He’ll be playing that one and many others when he heads back on the road at the end of the summer. You can get his full schedule right <a href="https://www.lukecombs.com/">here</a>.</p>

  <div class="component--youtube"
      data-element-id="youtube-player-cYytE44W"
      data-content-id="7Lb9dq-JZFI"
      data-autoplay-next-video="true"
      data-autoplay-video="false"
      data-playlist=""
      data-track-video-type="Editorial"
      data-track-video-location="article"
      data-track-video-title="Luke Combs - Beer Never Broke My Heart"
      data-track-video-duration="223"
      data-track-channel-name="LukeCombsVEVO"
      data-editable="inline"
      data-origsrc="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Lb9dq-JZFI">

    <iframe id="youtube-player-cYytE44W" type="text/html" width="640" height="360"
      src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7Lb9dq-JZFI?autoplay=0&origin=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Lb9dq-JZFI"
      frameborder="0"></iframe>
  </div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl/>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline>The little boy puts a lot of heart into his performance</subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[Toddler Sings 'Beer Never Broke My Heart' by Luke Combs]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/LukeCombs-7460b8e8-751c-4954-89f3-0f7866fcfc9f.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>false</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject" data-editable="inlinestuff">
    <div class="image-wrapper">
        
          <img src="https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/LukeCombs-8d31006c-9474-4868-bcaa-84c18022863e.jpg?width=800" alt="Luke Combs performs on stage during day 3 of the 2019 CMA Music Festival">
        
    </div>
      <figcaption itemprop="caption" class="image-figcaption">
        <span class="caption">Luke Combs</span>
        <cite class="credit">Photo credit Jason Kempin/Getty Images</cite>
      </figcaption>
</div>]]></lead>
			<category>Country</category>
			<category>Luke Combs</category>
			<dc:creator>Bob Diehl</dc:creator>
			<editorialFeeds>Country</editorialFeeds>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[QA Lois Lane Ezekiel Elliott May Sit Out 2019 Season Without New Deal]]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/sports/ezekiel-elliott-holdout-rumors-dallas-cowboys-contract-aug</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 15:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/sports/ezekiel-elliott-holdout-rumors-dallas-cowboys-contract-aug</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl/>
			<description><![CDATA[Read - Ezekiel Elliott may sit out 2019 season without new deal - and more NFL news and rumors on Radio.com.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p>Things still appear to be relatively cordial between the Dallas Cowboys and star running-back <a href="https://www.radio.com/topic/ezekiel-elliott">Ezekiel Elliott</a>, who is currently holding out in hopes of forcing the Cowboys to give him a new contract. But if there was any doubt about how serious the 24-year-old is about getting a new deal, that's quickly dissipating.</p>
  <p><a href="https://twitter.com/wingoz/status/1158725187531104256">Josina Anderson of <em>ESPN</em> reported</a> Tuesday morning that the two-time Pro-Bowler doesn't plan to play in 2019 under his current contract. Given that <a href="https://www.radio.com/topic/leveon-bell">Le'Veon Bell</a> sat out the entire 2018 season after the Pittsburgh Steelers franchise tagged him for a second consecutive season, it's hard to dismiss any threats from star running-backs not to play under their current contractual circumstances.</p>
  <p><a href="https://twitter.com/JosinaAnderson/status/1158727938151522304">Per Anderson</a>, the belief still is that Elliott will ultimately play in 2019. However, she says she reached out to Elliott's representatives in response to Hall of Famer Eric Dickerson <a href="https://twitter.com/undisputed/status/1158412058322280448?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1158412058322280448&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cbssports.com%2Fnfl%2Fnews%2Fezekiel-elliott-holdout-hall-of-famer-eric-dickerson-says-it-really-is-possible-star-rb-misses-games-per-agent%2F">saying Monday</a> that he had heard from Elliott's agent that &quot;it really is possible he will miss some games.&quot; This report didn't exactly squash that idea.</p>
  <p>Elliott is under contract for two more seasons, which perhaps incentives him to sit out if a new deal isn't reached. Not only do the Cowboys control Elliott for the next two seasons - when he's scheduled to make just shy of $13 million on his rookie deal - but they can franchise tag him for two additional seasons after that, just as the Steelers attempted to do with Bell. So there's a very real chance that Elliott wouldn't actually be able to become a free-agent until after his seventh NFL season, when his stock likely would be much lower than it is now.</p>
<div itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject" data-editable="inlinestuff">
    <div class="image-wrapper">
        
          <img src="https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/GettyImages1074760058-fc026d02-a3bb-49af-a002-e03ceff9d36e.jpg?width=800" alt="Ezekiel Elliott is entering his fourth NFL season. ">
        
    </div>
      <figcaption itemprop="caption" class="image-figcaption">
        <span class="caption">Ezekiel Elliott is entering his fourth NFL season.</span>
        <cite class="credit">Photo credit (Richard Rodriguez/Getty Images)</cite>
      </figcaption>
</div>  <p>If Elliott were to sit out the 2019 season, he would forfeit his chance to accrue a season towards free-agency, meaning the next time he played, he would still have two years left on his rookie deal. While that's a risk, <a href="https://www.radio.com/sports/nfl/3-nfl-takeaways-ahead-of-preseason-week-1">it's seemingly one worth taking</a> for Elliott, because given the nature of the running-back position, his stock likely will only go down the longer he spends in the league.</p>
  <p>Though Cowboys owner and general manager Jerry Jones <a href="https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2019/07/29/jerry-jones-you-dont-need-the-rushing-champ-to-win-a-super-bowl/">did wonder aloud</a> last week about whether a Super Bowl team needs an elite running-back, <a href="http://www.nfl.com/news/story/0ap3000001038988/article/jones-on-extending-zeke-dak-cooper-itll-happen">he calmly stated Monday</a> that he expects that the Cowboys will ultimately sign Elliott, quarterback <a href="https://www.radio.com/topic/dak-prescott">Dak Prescott</a> and wide receiver <a href="https://www.radio.com/topic/amari-cooper">Amari Cooper</a> to long-term deals. Both Prescott and Cooper, unlike Elliott, can become free-agents after the 2019 season.</p>
  <p>The No. 4 overall pick in the 2016 NFL Draft, Elliott has rushed for 4,048 yards in his first three NFL seasons, while leading the Cowboys to NFC East titles in 2016 and 2018.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl>https://www.radio.com/sports</stationUrl>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline></subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[Ezekiel Elliott May Sit Out Cowboys Season Without New Deal]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/GettyImages1090322720-fa6b618a-9115-4d6f-a4af-a9e9d1d5537d.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>false</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div class="component--brightcove">
  <div class="player">
        <iframe src="https://players.brightcove.net/5757251889001/9klBjvbUGf_default/index.html?videoId=6068241441001" allowfullscreen="" webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" style="width: 640px; height: 360px;"></iframe>
  </div>
</div>
]]></lead>
			<category>Ezekiel Elliott</category>
			<category>Dallas Cowboys</category>
			<dc:creator>Lois Lane</dc:creator>
			<dc:creator>Tim Kelly</dc:creator>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[QA: No <dc:creator> Nobel Laureate Toni Morrison Dead at 88]]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/articles/nobel-laureate-toni-morrison-dead-88</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 13:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/articles/nobel-laureate-toni-morrison-dead-88</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl>https://1010wins.radio.com/articles/nobel-laureate-toni-morrison-dead-88</syndicatedUrl>
			<description><![CDATA[Nobel laureate and author Toni Morrison has passed away at the age of 88. ]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p><strong>(</strong><a href="https://1010wins.radio.com/articles/nobel-laureate-toni-morrison-dead-88"><strong>1010 WINS/AP</strong></a><strong>) _ </strong>Nobel Prize-winning author Toni Morrison has died.</p>
  <p>Publisher Alfred A. Knopf says Morrison died Monday night at Montefiore Medical Center in New York. She was 88.    </p>
  <p>She was the first black woman to receive the Nobel literature prize, awarded in 1993.</p>
  <p>The Swedish academy <a href="https://1010wins.radio.com/articles/radiocom/robert-f-kennedys-granddaughter-dies-apparent-overdose">hailed her use of language</a> and her &quot;visionary force.''</p>
  <p>Her novel ``Beloved,'' in which a mother makes a tragic choice to murder her baby to save the girl from slavery, won the Pulitzer Prize for fiction in 1988.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl></stationUrl>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline></subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[Nobel Laureate Toni Morrison Dead at 88]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/ToniMorrison.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>false</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div class="component--verizon-media">
  <div class="player">
      <div class="player__video player__video--hidden-title">
      </div>
  </div>
</div>]]></lead>
			<category>National News</category>
			<category>toni morrison</category>
			<category>Obituary</category>
			<category>literature</category>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[LeBron James Headlines 2010's All-Decade NBA Team]]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/sports/nba/lebron-james-news-nba-all-decade-team-kevin-durant-kawhi-leonard</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 13:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/sports/nba/lebron-james-news-nba-all-decade-team-kevin-durant-kawhi-leonard</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl/>
			<description><![CDATA[Read - LeBron James Headlines 2010’s All-Decade NBA Team - and more NBA news and rumors on Radio.com. ]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p>At the outset of this decade, <a href="https://www.radio.com/topic/lebron-james">LeBron James</a> was still in his first stint with the Cleveland Cavaliers, was coming off of his second consecutive NBA MVP Award and had only appeared in the NBA Finals once. He’ll leave the decade as a four-time league MVP, three-time NBA Champion and almost inarguably one of the five best players in NBA history.</p>
  <p>NBA.com has added to James’ rich legacy, as he headlines their 2010’s <a href="https://www.nba.com/all-decade-team-best-players-2010s">All-Decade first team</a>. Every season this decade, James was an All-Star and named to the All-NBA team, with 2010 and 2019 the only two years he didn’t lead his team to an NBA Finals berth.</p>
  <p>James - who averaged 26.9 points per game, along with over seven-and-a-half rebounds and assists this decade - won back-to-back titles with <a href="https://www.radio.com/topic/dwyane-wade">Dwyane Wade</a> on the Miami Heat in 2011-12 and 2012-13.</p>
  <p>After four seasons in South Beach, James returned to Cleveland, where the Cavaliers appeared in the NBA Finals all four seasons of his second stint. In 2016-17, James led the Cavs back from a 3-1 deficit to the Golden State Warriors in the NBA Finals, winning his third NBA Finals MVP and helping to end 52-year championship drought among Cleveland’s major professional sports teams.</p>
  <p>While James dominated the NBA this decade, <a href="https://www.radio.com/topic/kevin-durant">Kevin Durant</a> established himself as an all-time great, averaging 28 points-per-game, 7.4 rebounds per contest and nearly four-and-a-half assists per game. That earned him a spot on the team as well.</p>
  <p>Durant’s Oklahoma City Thunder - which also included <a href="https://www.radio.com/topic/russell-westbrook">Russell Westbrook</a> and <a href="https://www.radio.com/topic/james-harden">James Harden</a> - lost to James and the Heat in five games in the 2011-12 NBA Finals. Though the Thunder appeared likely to become a mainstay in the NBA Finals, they never made it back to the series with Durant and Westbrook.</p>
<div itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject" data-editable="inlinestuff">
    <div class="image-wrapper">
        
          <img src="https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/GettyImages970200460-1-4b4595a0-0c3d-40f8-8c03-132131eb47de.jpg?width=800" alt="Kevin Durant won two NBA Finals MVPs with the Golden State Warriors. ">
        
    </div>
      <figcaption itemprop="caption" class="image-figcaption">
        <span class="caption">Kevin Durant won two NBA Finals MVPs with the Golden State Warriors.</span>
        <cite class="credit">Photo credit (Jason Miller/Getty Images)</cite>
      </figcaption>
</div>  <p>After blowing a 3-1 lead to the Golden State Warriors in the 2015-16 Western Conference Finals, Durant made the controversial decision to join the Warriors ahead of the 2016-17 season. For as much blowback as Durant may have received for his <a href="https://www.theplayerstribune.com/en-us/articles/kevin-durant-nba-free-agency-announcement">“next chapter,”</a> his three seasons in Golden State were wildly successful, as he won his first two NBA titles and was the NBA Finals MVP in both 2017 and 2018.</p>
  <p>Of course, one of the reasons the Warriors were such an attractive destination for Durant was the presence of <a href="https://www.radio.com/topic/steph-curry">Steph Curry</a>. Though Curry may not be in the class of James and Durant all-time, he had the biggest impact this decade on how the sport was played. From beyond the arc, Curry shot nearly 40 percent this decade, creating a lane as the greatest three-point shooter in the history of the sport and making three-point shooting sexy.</p>
  <p>Though not always the best individual player on his team, Curry was the face of the decade’s best team - the Golden State Warriors. Coming into this decade, the Warriors hadn’t appeared in the NBA Finals since the 1974-75 season, when Rick Barry led them to an NBA Finals victory. The Warriors ended the 2010s having won five consecutive Western Conference titles and three NBA Championships in the decade. Multiple Warriors teams this decade forced their way into the discussion for best team in NBA history, all of which employed Curry.</p>
  <p>Kawhi Leonard may be most remembered this decade for <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zIwh0njInPk">his quirky personality</a>, but he’s also a two-time NBA Finals MVP that <a href="https://www.sbnation.com/2019/4/29/18522085/kawhi-leonard-raptors-nba-playoffs-2019-dynasty-disrupt">ended the Miami Heat’s mini-dynasty</a> and may have helped to kill off the Warriors dynasty as well. Still just 28, Leonard led the Toronto Raptors to an NBA title in 2018-19, five years after leading Gregg Popovich and the San Antonio Spurs to their fifth title. He and James are the only two players to lead two different franchises to NBA titles this decade, which is perhaps fitting in a decade defined by player movement.</p>
  <p>Finally, the aforementioned Harden rounded out the 2010s All-Decade team, edging out Westbrook, who will once again be his teammate in 2019-20. While there's a debate to be had about how aesthetically pleasing or likely to lead to a championship Harden's style is, this is indisputable - he's one of the better scorers in NBA history. Harden made the All-NBA team six times this decade, while averaging 24.3 points per game with the Thunder and Houston Rockets.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl>https://www.radio.com/sports</stationUrl>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline></subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[LeBron James Headlines 2010's All-Decade NBA Team]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/GettyImages169876044-2-8d358a51-cd5b-47b7-bfbd-956fb1450f73.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>true</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div class="component--brightcove">
  <div class="player">
        <iframe src="https://players.brightcove.net/5757251889001/9klBjvbUGf_default/index.html?videoId=6023883106001" allowfullscreen="" webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" style="width: 640px; height: 360px;"></iframe>
  </div>
</div>
]]></lead>
			<category>Lebron James</category>
			<category>Kawhi Leonard</category>
			<category>James Harden</category>
			<category>Steph Curry</category>
			<category>Kevin Durant</category>
			<dc:creator>Tim Kelly</dc:creator>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[WORLD PREMIERE: Tool Inject a New Generation With 'Fear Inoculum']]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/music/rock/world-premiere-tool-return-with-fear-inoculum</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/music/rock/world-premiere-tool-return-with-fear-inoculum</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl/>
			<description><![CDATA[For the first time in 13 years, Tool returns with new music, the title track from their 5th album ‘Fear Inoculum.’]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p>13 years in the making, the time for <strong>Tool</strong> has arrived.</p>
  <p>On Wednesday August 7, the band officially reveals their first song since 2006, the epic title track to their upcoming 5<sup>th</sup> album, <em>Fear Inoculum</em>. The song is the first sample of the LP due out on August 30.</p>
<aside class="component--instagram-post">
  <blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/p/B0ycrhRn5ny/" data-instgrm-version="12" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"><div style="padding:16px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B0ycrhRn5ny/" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"> <div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"></div></div></div><div style="padding: 19% 0;"></div> <div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"><svg width="50px" height="50px" viewBox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"><g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"><g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"><g><path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"></path></g></g></g></svg></div><div style="padding-top: 8px;"> <div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"> View this post on Instagram</div></div><div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"><div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"></div></div><div style="margin-left: 8px;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"></div></div><div style="margin-left: auto;"> <div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"></div></div></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center; margin-bottom: 24px;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 224px;"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 144px;"></div></div></a><p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B0ycrhRn5ny/" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none;" target="_blank">A post shared by Tool (@toolmusic)</a> on <time style=" font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;" datetime="2019-08-05T16:05:13+00:00">Aug 5, 2019 at 9:05am PDT</time></p></div></blockquote>
</aside>
  <p>“Fear Inoculum” is a RADIO.COM World Premiere, which means you can hear it here all throughout the day on Wednesday August 7.</p>
  <p>In 2006, Tool topped the <a href="https://www.billboard.com/music/tool/chart-history/billboard-200">Billboard Chart</a> with <em>10,000 Days</em>, followed by extensive touring. Work seemed to begin shortly after on a follow-up, but was ultimately delayed by various circumstances and side-projects. However, the band seemed to officially enter the studio in 2018, with frontman <strong>Maynard James Keenan</strong> sparingly offering updates throughout the year.</p>
  <p>Tool would <a href="https://www.radio.com/blogs/tiana-timmerberg/watch-tool-live-debut-first-new-music-over-decade">debut two songs live</a> in May of 2019 at the <em>Welcome To Rockville Festival</em>, surprising fans with “Descending” and “Invincible.” Now, the usually elusive band has made all of their previous material available on all platforms, and is just days away from offering their first new album in 13 years.</p>
  <p>“A lot of weight lifted off my chest. The four of us are a lot of f***ing work” explained Keenan on <a href="http://podcasts.joerogan.net/podcasts/maynard-james-keenan-3"><em>The Joe Rogan Experience</em></a> last week, as he revealed the album title. “Everything is a f***ing committee meeting, and it always gets shut down.”</p>
  <p>Pre-order details for <em>Fear Inoculum</em> will be available on the <a href="https://toolband.com/">band’s website</a>, with the album due to arrive on August 30.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl/>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline>Hear the title track from the band’s long-awaited album on Wednesday August 7</subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[WORLD PREMIERE: Tool Return With 'Fear Inoculum']]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/ToolWorldPremiere-8d870fb8-0bc8-450a-ab74-7e3c44fa2e2f.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>true</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject" data-editable="inlinestuff">
    <div class="image-wrapper">
        
          <img src="https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/ToolWorldPremiere-2e13f1fe-d579-404f-a106-dc7249bd946a.jpg?width=800" alt="Tool World Premiere &quot;&#x27;Fear Inoculum&quot;">
        
    </div>
      <figcaption itemprop="caption" class="image-figcaption">
        
        <cite class="credit">Photo credit Tool | RADIO.COM</cite>
      </figcaption>
</div>]]></lead>
			<category>Rock</category>
			<category>Tool</category>
			<category>World Premiere</category>
			<dc:creator>Michael Cerio</dc:creator>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Mark Wahlberg: Why I'm Rooting for a Patriots-Cowboys Super Bowl Matchup]]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/blogs/lucy-burdge/tuesday-s-mashup-mark-wahlberg-explains-why-he-rooting-patriots-cowboys-super-bowl</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 11:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/blogs/lucy-burdge/tuesday-s-mashup-mark-wahlberg-explains-why-he-rooting-patriots-cowboys-super-bowl</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl>https://weei.radio.com/blogs/lucy-burdge/tuesday-s-mashup-mark-wahlberg-explains-why-he-rooting-patriots-cowboys-super-bowl</syndicatedUrl>
			<description><![CDATA[The ‘Wahlburgers’ star and Boston native shows up to the Dallas Cowboys practice and explains why his hometown allegiance may be split for this year’s NFL championship.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p><strong>(</strong><a href="https://weei.radio.com/blogs/lucy-burdge/tuesday-s-mashup-mark-wahlberg-explains-why-he-rooting-patriots-cowboys-super-bowl"><strong>WEEI</strong></a><strong>) --</strong> <a href="https://www.radio.com/topic/mark-wahlberg">Mark Wahlberg</a> grew up as a Patriots fan in Massachusetts but his recent business with the Cowboys could make him change his allegiance.</p>
  <p>Wahlberg and his family opened up a new Wahlburgers location at the Cowboys' practice facility and the actor said at Dallas’ <a href="https://www.radio.com/articles/news/ezekiel-elliott-heading-cabo-not-oxnard">training camp</a> on Saturday he “might have to change his &quot;blue&quot; and &quot;start wearing another shade.&quot;</p>
  <p>&quot;The Cowboys are showing me so much love,&quot; Wahlberg said. &quot;I don’t have a Wahlburgers at Gillette Stadium yet. I gotta re-evaluate my loyalty here.&quot;</p>
  <p>He also said a Cowboys-Patriots matchup would be a &quot;stress-free&quot; Super Bowl.</p>
  <p>&quot;That’s going to be a good Super Bowl matchup,&quot; he said. &quot;I’m calling it right now.&quot;</p>

  <div class="component--youtube"
      data-element-id="youtube-player-TDQW8ziM"
      data-content-id="xhAI2jM3SoE"
      data-autoplay-next-video=""
      data-autoplay-video=""
      data-playlist=""
      data-track-video-type="Editorial"
      data-track-video-location=""
      data-track-video-title="Mark Wahlberg: Talks Cowboys Vs Patriots | Dallas Cowboys 2019"
      data-track-video-duration="78"
      data-track-channel-name="Dallas Cowboys"
      data-editable="inline"
      data-origsrc="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xhAI2jM3SoE">

    <iframe id="youtube-player-TDQW8ziM" type="text/html" width="640" height="360"
      src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xhAI2jM3SoE?autoplay=0&origin=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xhAI2jM3SoE"
      frameborder="0"></iframe>
  </div>
  <p>Wahlberg famously left Super Bowl LI early and missed the Patriots’ historic 28-3 comeback.</p>
  <p> </p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl></stationUrl>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline></subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[Mark Wahlberg is Rooting for a Patriots-Cowboys Super Bowl]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/wahlberg_%20Bob%20DeChiara-USA%20TODAY%20Sports.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>false</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div class="component--brightcove">
  <div class="player">
        <iframe src="https://players.brightcove.net/5757251889001/9klBjvbUGf_default/index.html?videoId=6065823067001" allowfullscreen="" webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" style="width: 640px; height: 360px;"></iframe>
  </div>
</div>
]]></lead>
			<category>Robert Kraft</category>
			<category>New England Patriots</category>
			<category>Dallas Cowboys</category>
			<category>Mark Wahlberg</category>
			<category>NFL</category>
			<category>Football</category>
			<category>Entertainment</category>
			<dc:creator>Lucy Burdge</dc:creator>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[QA: No <dc:creator> EXCLUSIVE: 'Bachelor' Alum Chelsea Roy Reveals Who She Left 'Paradise' With]]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/blogs/exclusive-bachelor-alum-chelsea-roy-reveals-who-she-really-left-paradise-and-other-juicy-show</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 09:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/blogs/exclusive-bachelor-alum-chelsea-roy-reveals-who-she-really-left-paradise-and-other-juicy-show</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl>https://mix1041.radio.com/blogs/exclusive-bachelor-alum-chelsea-roy-reveals-who-she-really-left-paradise-and-other-juicy-show</syndicatedUrl>
			<description><![CDATA[See what really happened on Season 5 of “Bachelor in Paradise” for Chelsea Roy. ]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p>(<a href="https://mix1041.radio.com/blogs/exclusive-bachelor-alum-chelsea-roy-reveals-who-she-really-left-paradise-and-other-juicy-show"><strong>MIX 104.1</strong></a>) - Attention Bachelor Nation! Chelsea Roy may have received the first impression rose on Arie Luyendyk's season of &quot;The Bachelor&quot;<em> </em>but today, she definitely stealing our attention. The reality show alum spilled all the juicy show secrets, especially when it came to what went down on Season 5 of &quot;Bachelor In Paradise.&quot;</p>
  <p>"There is a lot that they don't show just because there are so many couples, there's so much drama going on, so they are trying to<a href="https://mix1041.radio.com/articles/radiocom/modern-family-cast-recreate-10-year-old-photo" target="_blank"> make this show short and sweet</a> but grab your attention" she told RADIO.COM’s Karson & Kennedy from Mix 104.1. "My story was definitely not shown -- towards the end they actually...made it look like I was trying to steal Kamil from Annaliese!" </p>
  <p>When asked if she ever met a man that she fell for from &quot;The Bachelor&quot;<em> </em>or &quot;Bachelor In Paradise,&quot; she revealed, &quot;I did, but they didn't show it!&quot; To clarify, it was definitely NOT Arie! Well, as luck would have it, someone ended up coming to &quot;Paradise&quot; the same night as all the Kamil drama, who she also said she wasn't interested in at all.</p>
  <p>&quot;That same night someone came to &quot;Paradise&quot; to rescue me. Somebody that I couldn't stop thinking about and somebody that didn't get my rose because I <a href="https://mix1041.radio.com/blogs/eric-donnelly/twitters-newest-viral-trend-texting-your-number-neighbor-and-sharing-response">was playing my card safe.</a>&quot; Roy ended up dating this person for a few months, but ended up calling it quits because the distance wasn't working. Before opening up about who it was, she stated, &quot;You guys are not going to believe this, I'm going to get judged!&quot;</p>
  <p>You'll never guess who this man was.........IT WAS NICK SPETSAS!</p>
<aside class="component--tweet">
  <blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Nick Spetsas<br>Age: 27<br>Hometown: Orlando, Florida<br>Occupation: Attorney <a href="https://t.co/uqIneDX0tR">pic.twitter.com/uqIneDX0tR</a></p>&mdash; Bachelor Nation (@bachelorn234) <a href="https://twitter.com/bachelorn234/status/998250581226553344?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 20, 2018</a></blockquote>

</aside>
  <p>If you follow Reality Steve at all, you may have seen some of his spoilers of this duo together from June 2018. &quot;[We dated&gt; a couple months, but then I realized that distance was becoming an issue because we were both <a href="https://mix1041.radio.com/blogs/danielle-pieroni/bachelorette-aftermath-jed-wyatt-tells-his-side-story">settling into our careers in our respective states</a>...unfortunately it didn't work out.&quot; Nick Speastas, &quot;the Italian lawyer from Jersey now living in Florida,&quot; originally came into the franchise on Becca's season of &quot;The Bachelorette&quot;<em> </em>and was eliminated in the 4th week<em>.</em> Roy resides in Portland, ME and Spestas is still a lawyer down in Miami, FL.</p>
  <p>Roy also discussed what it was like being a mother and going on this show. "It's definitely difficult dating with a child, which is why I took advantage of the show because I could disconnect a little bit and really focus on what my needs were." </p>
  <p>We also got to learn a lot more juicy secrets about the show and Roy's answers definitely might debunk some common myths about whether what happens on the show is truly real love. "There are people that go on and they are definitely acting, but they don't last long. If you are open to understanding the amount of time you have disconnected from the world and actually spend time investigating and gettiing to know someone, it definitely works." There's no phones, no newspapers, no nothing....</p>
  <p>"You can't call mom to cry -- you don't have your normal support system that you have to figure out for yourself, and by doing that you're actually figuring out with somebody else because you have no choice but to talk. It really is something that works!"</p>
  <p>Listen to the full interview above to hear even more secrets from the show. Until next time Bachelor Nation.....</p>
<aside class="component--instagram-post">
  <blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/p/By_cxhXgxXK/" data-instgrm-version="12" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"><div style="padding:16px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/By_cxhXgxXK/" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"> <div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"></div></div></div><div style="padding: 19% 0;"></div> <div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"><svg width="50px" height="50px" viewBox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"><g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"><g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"><g><path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"></path></g></g></g></svg></div><div style="padding-top: 8px;"> <div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"> View this post on Instagram</div></div><div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"><div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"></div></div><div style="margin-left: 8px;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"></div></div><div style="margin-left: auto;"> <div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"></div></div></div></a> <p style=" margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/By_cxhXgxXK/" style=" color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;" target="_blank">This is 30 something! 🥰. . . . . . Thank you @hiddenpond for the wonderful hospitality and to all of those who were apart making it such a memorable celebration! ♥️</a></p> <p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;">A post shared by <a href="https://www.instagram.com/chelsea_roy_/" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px;" target="_blank"> C h e l s e a  R o y</a> (@chelsea_roy_) on <time style=" font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;" datetime="2019-06-22T00:09:32+00:00">Jun 21, 2019 at 5:09pm PDT</time></p></div></blockquote>
</aside>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl></stationUrl>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline></subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA['Bachelor' Alum Chelsea Roy Reveals Secrets From 'Paradise']]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/chelsea%20roy.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>false</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div class="component--brightcove">
  <div class="player">
        <iframe src="https://players.brightcove.net/5757251889001/9klBjvbUGf_default/index.html?videoId=6068229203001" allowfullscreen="" webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" style="width: 640px; height: 360px;"></iframe>
  </div>
</div>
]]></lead>
			<category>Bachelor</category>
			<category>Bachelorette</category>
			<category>Bachelor In Paradise</category>
			<category>Chelsea Roy</category>
			<editorialFeeds>Trending</editorialFeeds>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Mets' Robinson Cano Has Torn Hamstring]]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/articles/mets-robinson-cano-has-torn-hamstring</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/articles/mets-robinson-cano-has-torn-hamstring</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl>https://wfan.radio.com/articles/mets-robinson-cano-has-torn-hamstring</syndicatedUrl>
			<description><![CDATA[For the third time this season, Robinson Cano is on the injured list.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p><strong>(</strong><a href="https://wfan.radio.com/articles/mets-robinson-cano-has-torn-hamstring"><strong>WFAN</strong></a><strong>) --</strong> For the third time this season, Robinson Cano is on the injured list.</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.radio.com/topic/new-york-mets">Mets</a> initially announced Monday they placed the 36-year-old second baseman on the 10-day IL with a left hamstring strain, but that diagnosis has now gotten worse. The team announced Monday evening that an MRI showed that Cano has a torn hamstring. Cano suffered the injury while running the bases in the fourth inning of the Mets' 13-2 win over the Pittsburgh Pirates on Sunday.</p>
  <p>The injury comes just as the Mets and Cano were both on hot streaks. The Mets have won nine of their last 10 to climb back into playoff contention, and Cano was 7-for-11 (.636) in his last three games.</p>
<div itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject" data-editable="inlinestuff">
    <div class="image-wrapper">
        
          <img src="https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/CANO_3.jpg?width=800" alt="  Pirates shortstop Kevin Newman tags out Mets second baseman Robinson Cano after Cano suffered an apparent hamstring injury running the bases during the fourth inning at PNC Park in Pittsburgh. ">
        
    </div>
      <figcaption itemprop="caption" class="image-figcaption">
        
        <cite class="credit">Photo credit Charles LeClaire/USA TODAY Images</cite>
      </figcaption>
</div>  <p>Surgery isn't required, but there is no timetable for Cano's return. That 10-day injured list won't be long enough for him, and he may not even be able to return this season</p>
  <p>Cano was sent to the injured list in May with a quad strain, and then he aggravated the injury in his first game back on June 5, resulting in another IL stint.</p>
  <p>The eight-time All-Star, who was acquired in an offseason trade with the Seattle Mariners, is batting .252 with 10 home runs and 32 RBIs this season.</p>
  <p>The Mets recalled infielder Luis Guillorme from Triple-A Syracuse to fill Cano's roster spot. New York also called up pitcher Walker Lockett to serve as the 26th man for Monday's home doubleheader against the Marlins. The right-hander will start the second game. </p>
  <p><em><strong>Listen to Mets games this season on the team's new flagship station -- our sister station -- <a href="http://wcbs880.radio.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">WCBS 880 AM</a>.</strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl></stationUrl>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline></subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[Mets' Robinson Cano Has Torn Hamstring]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/CANO2_0.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>false</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div class="component--brightcove">
  <div class="player">
        <iframe src="https://players.brightcove.net/5757251889001/9klBjvbUGf_default/index.html?videoId=6052099765001" allowfullscreen="" webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" style="width: 640px; height: 360px;"></iframe>
  </div>
</div>
]]></lead>
			<category>Robinson Cano</category>
			<category>New York Mets</category>
			<category>All Local</category>
			<category>Watch Sports</category>
			<category>Breaking News</category>
			<dc:creator>Ryan Chatelain</dc:creator>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Unite Your Office With These Team Building Activities]]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/news/small-business-pulse/unite-office-team-building-activities</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 20:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/news/small-business-pulse/unite-office-team-building-activities</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl></syndicatedUrl>
			<description><![CDATA[A small business can thrive when their employers create a collaboration of activities that establish stronger employee bonds and improve group cohesion.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p>Company leaders want to create an environment where their staff is working together as a cohesive unit. Small businesses can thrive when their employers create a collaboration of activities that establish stronger employee bonds and improve group cohesion. Creating an office environment where employees are efficiently working as a team may require certain key moves in order to foster such a satisfying situation. The following are five proven strategies to make that happen.</p>
  <p><strong>Sharing accomplishments</strong><br />When certain members of your team are standouts, such as meeting lofty goals or completing extracurricular training, why not give these high achievers a group shout out? In other words, take a break from job duties to gather together and share in the experience, even if that simply means indulging in an extra coffee break toward the end of the workday.</p>
  <p><strong>Group dinner or happy hour</strong><br />Congregate even when the workday is done. Hosting your staff at a dinner or happy hour in a relaxing environment is an effective way to bring your team closer. Employees will welcome an atmosphere where they can be comfortable socializing with co-workers in which the conversation doesn’t have to be about work. Your employees can get to know each other on a personal level over a great meal, either in a restaurant, bar or at someone’s house.</p>
  <p><strong>Get out of the office</strong><br />Make it a requirement to get out of the office once or twice a year so that your employees can attend a relatable industry event or training session in which your whole crew takes part. Not only will this time away from the regular routine inspire new ideas and hopefully result in higher profits, but the camaraderie among your workers should also flourish.</p>
  <p><strong>Volunteer</strong><br />Make it a point to encourage your team to volunteer as a group for a worthy cause. For instance, you could all take part in an arranged event, such as serving the homeless at the local soup kitchen. Holding your own event is another option, like setting up a Saturday car wash where the proceeds are donated to a local shelter.</p>
  <p><strong>Friendly competition</strong><br />Another way to build your team’s spirit is to get everyone involved in a singular physical activity in which sportsmanship is the common goal. Hold an office softball game or get the group to get their bowling game on. Place a foosball or ping pong table in a common area. Whatever physical activity you choose, remind your crew that it’s not who wins that counts, but rather the amount of fun that can be had with your office mates while playing a game.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl/>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline></subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[Unite Your Office With These Team Building Activities]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/Office-Unity-1b528c1a-092f-40f0-ae43-f6fdf9d26cdf.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured></featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject" data-editable="inlinestuff">
    <div class="image-wrapper">
        
          <img src="https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/Office-Unity-4aab8046-130f-441f-a5f4-99fc73ad1730.jpg?width=800" alt="Office Unity">
        
    </div>
      <figcaption itemprop="caption" class="image-figcaption">
        
        <cite class="credit">Photo credit Rawpixel/Getty Images</cite>
      </figcaption>
</div>]]></lead>
			<category>Human Resources</category>
			<category>Small Business Growth</category>
			<category>Employee Relations</category>
			<category>Employee Satisfaction</category>
			<dc:creator>Jane Lasky</dc:creator>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Colts QB Andrew Luck: I ‘Certainly’ Expect to Play Week 1]]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/sports/nfl/andrew-luck-i-certainly-expect-to-play-week-1</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 19:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/sports/nfl/andrew-luck-i-certainly-expect-to-play-week-1</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl/>
			<description><![CDATA[While Colts head coach Frank Reich doesn’t expect to have their franchise quarterback available to practice for at least another week, Luck himself is feeling more optimistic.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p>The Indianapolis Colts won’t get to ease into the 2019 NFL season, as they’ll open the season in Los Angeles on Sept. 8 against the Chargers, who are dark-horse Super Bowl contenders. <a href="https://kcbsnews.radio.com/tag/andrew-luck">Andrew Luck</a> still says the plan is for him to be under center for the Colts that day.</p>
  <p>Colts head coach <a href="https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/27316496/colts-say-luck-calf-least-another-week?platform=amp">Frank Reich said</a> this past weekend that the team doesn’t expect to have their franchise quarterback available to practice for at least another week. With just over a month until their first regular season game, Luck remains optimistic.</p>
  <p>“I certainly believe I will [be ready for Week 1],” <a href="https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2019/08/05/don-banks-dies-nfl-fmia-peter-king/">Luck said</a> to Peter King of <em>Football Morning in America</em>. “That’s certainly the goal.”</p>
  <p>There do appear to be some qualifiers in Luck’s assessment of whether he’ll be ready for Week 1. Given Luck’s injury history, that will lead to some speculation that the soon-to-be 30-year-old’s calf injury has left him less than certain about whether he’ll be available to open the season.</p>
  <p>Surgery on his throwing shoulder ultimately cost Luck the entire 2017 season. <a href="https://www.indystar.com/story/sports/nfl/colts/2018/09/04/indianapolis-colts-andrew-luck-shoulder-scared-my-core-wouldnt-play-football-again/1184529002/">He later admitted</a> that following a slew of injuries, he wasn’t sure if he would ever be physically capable of playing in the NFL again.</p>
  <p>Luck did ultimately return in 2018, and did so in grand fashion. The 2012 No. 1 overall pick tossed 39 touchdowns in 2018, while throwing for 4,593 yards. A year after going 4-12 without Luck, the Colts won seven of their last eight regular season games in 2018, allowing them to win the final Wild Card spot in the AFC. Luck was voted the Comeback Player of the Year.</p>
  <p>But even after playing all 16 games in 2018, there’s an understandable sense of uneasiness from Luck about his latest injury.</p>
  <p>“At times I do worry about it. It can be frustrating. The arc of an injury, whether it’s a big surgical one or something you’re rehabbing through. But no, because I’ve improved. Maybe I’m not improving as fast as I want and missing things is no fun. It eats at you. But I do know at the end of the day if I’m getting the most out of myself, if I’m being the best I can that day, then that’s what I need to do.”</p>
  <p>As noted in this week’s edition of <a href="https://www.radio.com/sports/nfl/3-nfl-takeaways-ahead-of-preseason-week-1">three NFL takeaways</a>, the AFC South has a chance to be the most competitive division in football in 2019. A year ago, the Colts went 10-6, which allowed them to finish second to the division champion Houston Texans and a game above the 9-7 Tennessee Titans. The Jacksonville Jaguars were the only team in the division that finished with a losing record, and that came a year after they made it to the AFC Championship. With former Super Bowl MVP Nick Foles now under center, the Jaguars expect to return to the postseason in 2019.</p>
  <p>If Luck isn’t ready to play Week 1, the Colts do appear to be in a good situation with Jacoby Brissett as their backup. While Brissett has just a 5-12 record as a starter, he’s thrown 13 touchdowns and just seven picks in his NFL career. Notably, the Colts <a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/sports/patriots/2018/08/18/sunfoot/a1OmL7fVrCgdYtsjSyuFOI/story.html?p1=Article_Recirculation_Pos4">reportedly turned down an offer</a> of a second-round pick for Brissett ahead of the 2018 season presumably because they feel confident about his ability to step in for Luck.</p>
  <p>Even if Luck is able to start Week 1, a slow start in 2019 could potentially damage the Colts playoff chances in such a competitive division. The good news for Luck and the Colts is that only one of their first five games comes against a divisional opponent - Week 2 against the Titans.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl/>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline></subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[Colts QB Andrew Luck: I ‘Certainly’ Expect to Play Week 1]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/GettyImages1078853602-1ed7488a-6d82-4294-8125-e639621f9023.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>false</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div class="component--brightcove">
  <div class="player">
        <iframe src="https://players.brightcove.net/5757251889001/9klBjvbUGf_default/index.html?videoId=6068304206001" allowfullscreen="" webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" style="width: 640px; height: 360px;"></iframe>
  </div>
</div>
]]></lead>
			<category>Andrew Luck</category>
			<category>Indianapolis Colts</category>
			<category>Frank Reich</category>
			<category>NFL</category>
			<category>Football</category>
			<dc:creator>Tim Kelly</dc:creator>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[R. Kelly Faces 2 New Sex Crime Charges in Minnesota]]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/articles/r-kelly-faces-2-new-sex-crime-charges-minnesota-alleged-2001-encounter-juvenile</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 19:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/articles/r-kelly-faces-2-new-sex-crime-charges-minnesota-alleged-2001-encounter-juvenile</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl>https://1010wins.radio.com/articles/r-kelly-faces-2-new-sex-crime-charges-minnesota-alleged-2001-encounter-juvenile</syndicatedUrl>
			<description><![CDATA[R. Kelly faces 2 new sex crime charges in Minnesota for alleged 2001 encounter with juvenile … ]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p><strong>(</strong><a href="https://1010wins.radio.com/articles/r-kelly-faces-2-new-sex-crime-charges-minnesota-alleged-2001-encounter-juvenile"><strong>1010 WINS</strong></a><strong>) -- </strong><a href="https://www.radio.com/topic/r-kelly"><strong>R. Kelly</strong></a> is now facing two new charges -- in Minnesota -- Hennepin County Attorney Mike Freeman announced Monday afternoon at a press conference in Minneapolis.</p>
  <p>R. Kelly has been charged with 2 sex crime counts for incidents allegedly occurring in July 2001, Freeman said.</p>
  <p>The victim <a href="https://www.radio.com/articles/r-kelly-pleads-not-guilty-sex-trafficking-charges">was a juvenile at the time.</a></p>
  <p>He said the victim alleges that she approached R. Kelly to get an autograph at an event at a mall, and he offered her $200 to dance with him in his hotel room. She also alleges the singer had sexual contact with her. Freeman said, though, "no intercourse" took place. </p>
  <p>Freeman said since R. Kelly is in custody in New York City, it is unknown when he would come to Minnesota.</p>
  <p>Freeman did add that considering everything else R. Kelly is facing criminally, there may never be a trial in Minnesota.</p>
  <p>Still, he said, &quot;We are going to make sure justice happens in Minnesota ... We felt we had more than enough (to bring charges against R. Kelly).&quot;</p>
  <p>As to what took so long to come forward, Freeman said the alleged victim was "embarrassed at the time." </p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl></stationUrl>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline></subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[R. Kelly Faces 2 New Sex Crime Charges in Minnesota]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/AP19054347601185.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>false</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject" data-editable="inlinestuff">
    <div class="image-wrapper">
        
          <img src="https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/AP19054347601185.jpg?width=800" alt="R. Kelly ">
        
    </div>
      <figcaption itemprop="caption" class="image-figcaption">
        
        <cite class="credit">Photo credit Chicago Police Dept. via AP</cite>
      </figcaption>
</div>]]></lead>
			<category>R. Kelly</category>
			<dc:creator>David Caplan </dc:creator>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Slipknot Shares New Single 'Birth of the Cruel']]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/music/rock/slipknot-shares-new-single-birth-of-the-cruel</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 19:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/music/rock/slipknot-shares-new-single-birth-of-the-cruel</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl/>
			<description><![CDATA[Slipknot Shares New Single ‘Birth of the Cruel’]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p><strong>Slipknot</strong> has shared a new single just days away from the release of their highly-anticipated sixth studio album.</p>
  <p>The video for “Birth of the Cruel” also features <strong>Corey Taylor</strong> and company in their white summer jumpsuit look and a closer look at their new masks.</p>
  <p>The track is the third single from <em>We Are Not Your Kind</em>, which will be released on Friday. The band is already on the road for their Knotfest Roadshow with special guests <strong>Volbeat</strong>, <strong>Gojira</strong> and <strong>Behemoth</strong>. Get the full list of dates <a href="https://www.slipknot1.com/events">here</a>.</p>
  <p>For more Slipknot spirit, check out the band’s new <a href="https://craftshack.com/products/slipknot-no-9-whiskey?fbclid=IwAR0T8SkZjT7obdZavWJ6aPWeEr2DjlXYs0dN1RRprwSaU5Ylhnuq7eAGmaM">whiskey</a> and their new <a href="https://www.radio.com/music/rock/slipknot-guns-n-roses-face-filters-available-on-facebook">face filters</a> on Facebook. The social network has unveiled a different one for all nine members, as well as a black hood with the Slipknot logo.</p>
<aside class="component--facebook-post">
  <div class="fb-post" data-href="https://www.facebook.com/slipknot/videos/506300563438831/" data-width="552"><blockquote cite="https://www.facebook.com/slipknot/videos/506300563438831/" class="fb-xfbml-parse-ignore"><p>Wear The Masks 🎪 | #WeAreNotYourKind</p>Posted by <a href="https://www.facebook.com/slipknot/">Slipknot</a> on&nbsp;<a href="https://www.facebook.com/slipknot/videos/506300563438831/">Wednesday, July 31, 2019</a></blockquote></div>
  <script src="//connect.facebook.net/en_US/all.js#xfbml=1&amp;version=v2.3"/>
</aside>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl/>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline>The video features a closer look at their new masks</subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[Slipknot Shares New Single 'Birth of the Cruel']]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/slipknot-1b7744d0-511b-4811-b28d-2696e0da6e66.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>false</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[
  <div class="component--youtube"
      data-element-id="youtube-player-CsFX7d7G"
      data-content-id="MGbjB0eVvko"
      data-autoplay-next-video="true"
      data-autoplay-video="false"
      data-playlist=""
      data-track-video-type="Editorial"
      data-track-video-location="article"
      data-track-video-title="Slipknot - Birth Of The Cruel (Vertical Video)"
      data-track-video-duration="276"
      data-track-channel-name="Slipknot"
      data-editable="inline"
      data-origsrc="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MGbjB0eVvko">

    <iframe id="youtube-player-CsFX7d7G" type="text/html" width="640" height="360"
      src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/MGbjB0eVvko?autoplay=0&origin=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MGbjB0eVvko"
      frameborder="0"></iframe>
  </div>
]]></lead>
			<category>Slipknot</category>
			<category>Rock</category>
			<dc:creator>Bob Diehl</dc:creator>
			<editorialFeeds>Rock</editorialFeeds>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Sophie Turner Snuggles New Pup After Death of Dog Waldo]]></title>
			<link>https://www.radio.com/music/entertainment-news/sophie-turner-snugs-new-pup-after-death-of-dog-waldo</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 19:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.radio.com/music/entertainment-news/sophie-turner-snugs-new-pup-after-death-of-dog-waldo</guid>
			<syndicatedUrl/>
			<description><![CDATA[The Game of Thrones start and her Jonas brother husband were seen at their home in Miami over the weekend, cuddling an adorable golden retriever puppy, seemingly the new addition to their family, just about a week after the death of their dog Waldo Picasso.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[  <p><a href="https://www.radio.com/topic/sophie-turner">Sophie Turner</a> has a fresh case of puppy love.</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.radio.com/topic/game-of-thrones"><em>Game of Thrones</em></a> star was seen getting some snugs in with a new dog over the weekend at the Miami home she shares with rocker husband <a href="https://www.radio.com/topic/joe-jonas">Joe Jonas</a>.</p>
<aside class="component--tweet">
  <blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SophieTurner?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#SophieTurner</a> gets puppy snuggles from a new dog after the death of Waldo<a href="https://t.co/s6sax6OYc7">https://t.co/s6sax6OYc7</a> <a href="https://t.co/a5pGZkq0Ku">pic.twitter.com/a5pGZkq0Ku</a></p>&mdash; ET Canada (@ETCanada) <a href="https://twitter.com/ETCanada/status/1157835302955900929?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 4, 2019</a></blockquote>

</aside>
  <p>The mini golden retriever appears to be a new member of the family. Turner was seen cradling the puppy like a baby, sporting a dark green, two-piece bathing suit and wrapped in a towel.</p>
  <p>She was also seen holding the dog earlier in the weekend while climbing off the Jonas Brothers jet in an Instagram story video posted by Jonas’ brother and bandmate, <a href="https://www.radio.com/topic/nick-jonas" target="_blank">Nick Jonas</a>.</p>
<aside class="component--tweet">
  <blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Mr and Mrs Jonas <a href="https://t.co/uyoL5ywSpb">pic.twitter.com/uyoL5ywSpb</a></p>&mdash; J O E  J O N A S (@joejonas) <a href="https://twitter.com/joejonas/status/1146623896059146241?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 4, 2019</a></blockquote>

</aside>
  <p>The shots of the canine cuddling are the latest in the fuzzy wuzzy rollercoaster of emotional ups and downs since the newlyweds <a href="https://www.radio.com/articles/sophie-turner-and-joe-jonas-marry-again-france-ceremony">tied the knot</a> in a lavish ceremony in France back in June, a picture of which Joe <a href="https://www.radio.com/music/see-sophie-turner-and-joe-jonas-first-wedding-photo">shared</a> with the caption, “Mr and Mrs Jonas.”</p>
  <p>Late last month, Turner and Jonas lost their former dog Waldo Picasso in a <a href="https://www.radio.com/music/sophie-turner-and-joe-jonas-dog-dies-in-freak-accident">“freak accident”</a> when the dog ran into the street while out on a walk in New York.</p>
  <p>The couple paid tribute to their late pet shortly after with matching dog tattoos <a href="https://www.radio.com/music/entertainment-news/sophie-turner-and-joe-jonas-get-matching-dog-tattoos">last Tuesday</a>.</p>
<aside class="component--instagram-post">
  <blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/p/B0hAkxjhKU8/" data-instgrm-version="12" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"><div style="padding:16px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B0hAkxjhKU8/" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"> <div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"></div></div></div><div style="padding: 19% 0;"></div> <div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"><svg width="50px" height="50px" viewBox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"><g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"><g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"><g><path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"></path></g></g></g></svg></div><div style="padding-top: 8px;"> <div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"> View this post on Instagram</div></div><div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"></div> <div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"><div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"></div> <div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"></div></div><div style="margin-left: 8px;"> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"></div></div><div style="margin-left: auto;"> <div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"></div> <div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"></div> <div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"></div></div></div></a> <p style=" margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;"> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B0hAkxjhKU8/" style=" color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;" target="_blank">R.I.P. my little angel.</a></p> <p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;">A post shared by <a href="https://www.instagram.com/joejonas/" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px;" target="_blank"> J O E J O N A S</a> (@joejonas) on <time style=" font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;" datetime="2019-07-29T21:28:42+00:00">Jul 29, 2019 at 2:28pm PDT</time></p></div></blockquote>
</aside>
  <p>“R.I.P. my little angel,” Joe Jonas captioned an Instagram photo of his new <a href="https://www.radio.com/music/gallery/addicted-to-ink-5-huge-pop-stars-that-cant-get-enough-tattoos">ink</a>.</p>
  <p>The couple was so distraught by the death of their pup that they waited two full days to report the incident.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<stationUrl/>
			<stationTitle></stationTitle>
			<subHeadline></subHeadline>
			<seoHeadline><![CDATA[Sophie Turner Snuggles New Pup After Death of Dog Waldo]]></seoHeadline>
			<coverImage>https://images.radio.com/aiu-media/GettyImages1153778132-3c06cdf6-8196-4444-bbab-a70fafa1131f.jpg</coverImage>
			<featured>false</featured>
			<lead><![CDATA[<div class="component--brightcove">
  <div class="player">
        <iframe src="https://players.brightcove.net/5757251889001/9klBjvbUGf_default/index.html?videoId=6068306230001" allowfullscreen="" webkitallowfullscreen="" mozallowfullscreen="" style="width: 640px; height: 360px;"></iframe>
  </div>
</div>
]]></lead>
			<category>Sophie Turner</category>
			<category>Joe Jonas</category>
			<category>Nick Jonas</category>
			<category>Jonas Brothers</category>
			<category>Entertainment</category>
			<category>Game of Thrones</category>
			<dc:creator>Eldis Sula</dc:creator>
			<editorialFeeds>Trending</editorialFeeds>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>